{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762160066","data":{"timestamp":" 947762160065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762160684","data":{"timestamp":" 947762160683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762160918","data":{"timestamp":" 947762160918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762161527","data":{"timestamp":" 947762161526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762162305","data":{"timestamp":" 947762162305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762163307","data":{"timestamp":" 947762163306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762163960","data":{"timestamp":" 947762163959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762165148","data":{"timestamp":" 947762165147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762165897","data":{"timestamp":" 947762165896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" MIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762167148","data":{"timestamp":" 947762167148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" ILIFUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762167971","data":{"timestamp":" 947762167971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" ULIMWENGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762168462","data":{"timestamp":" 947762168461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762169394","data":{"timestamp":" 947762169394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762178796","data":{"timestamp":" 947762178796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762180027","data":{"timestamp":" 947762180027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762183465","data":{"timestamp":" 947762183465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762185321","data":{"timestamp":" 947762185320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762185480","data":{"timestamp":" 947762185480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762188822","data":{"timestamp":" 947762188821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762191825","data":{"timestamp":" 947762191824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762192779","data":{"timestamp":" 947762192779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762258515","data":{"timestamp":" 947762258515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762270467","data":{"timestamp":" 947762270467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 22578c71-d7d6-4902-81a9-61a312f026ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762294562","data":{"timestamp":" 947762294562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762302371","data":{"timestamp":" 947762302371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762303683","data":{"timestamp":" 947762303682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762306154","data":{"timestamp":" 947762306154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762307781","data":{"timestamp":" 947762307781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" MIKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762309421","data":{"timestamp":" 947762309421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762311638","data":{"timestamp":" 947762311638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762312850","data":{"timestamp":" 947762312850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762314671","data":{"timestamp":" 947762314670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762317323","data":{"timestamp":" 947762317322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762319560","data":{"timestamp":" 947762319559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762320773","data":{"timestamp":" 947762320772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762322280","data":{"timestamp":" 947762322279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762324138","data":{"timestamp":" 947762324138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762326071","data":{"timestamp":" 947762326071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762327912","data":{"timestamp":" 947762327911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762336767","data":{"timestamp":" 947762336767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" START_ILIFUNIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762339577","data":{"timestamp":" 947762339577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762341400","data":{"timestamp":" 947762341400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762342565","data":{"timestamp":" 947762342564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762344680","data":{"timestamp":" 947762344680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762346601","data":{"timestamp":" 947762346601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762349762","data":{"timestamp":" 947762349761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762351156","data":{"timestamp":" 947762351156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762352410","data":{"timestamp":" 947762352410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762354984","data":{"timestamp":" 947762354983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762356809","data":{"timestamp":" 947762356809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762358543","data":{"timestamp":" 947762358543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762359160","data":{"timestamp":" 947762359160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762359396","data":{"timestamp":" 947762359395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762359991","data":{"timestamp":" 947762359990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762360755","data":{"timestamp":" 947762360755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762361740","data":{"timestamp":" 947762361740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762362374","data":{"timestamp":" 947762362374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762363550","data":{"timestamp":" 947762363549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762364284","data":{"timestamp":" 947762364284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" MIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762365518","data":{"timestamp":" 947762365518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" ILIFUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762366323","data":{"timestamp":" 947762366323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" ULIMWENGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762366810","data":{"timestamp":" 947762366809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762367725","data":{"timestamp":" 947762367725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762371846","data":{"timestamp":" 947762371846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" START_NAYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762374981","data":{"timestamp":" 947762374981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762375678","data":{"timestamp":" 947762375678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762377185","data":{"timestamp":" 947762377184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762378496","data":{"timestamp":" 947762378496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHONGOKA"," userResponse":" START_ILICHONGOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762380322","data":{"timestamp":" 947762380322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHONGOKA"," userResponse":" MIKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762382183","data":{"timestamp":" 947762382183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHONGOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762384571","data":{"timestamp":" 947762384570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" ILICHONGOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762386665","data":{"timestamp":" 947762386665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762388518","data":{"timestamp":" 947762388517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762390300","data":{"timestamp":" 947762390300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762390795","data":{"timestamp":" 947762390795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762391542","data":{"timestamp":" 947762391541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762392756","data":{"timestamp":" 947762392756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHONGOKA"," userResponse":" ILICHONGOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762393867","data":{"timestamp":" 947762393867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" MAWINGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762398476","data":{"timestamp":" 947762398475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762399885","data":{"timestamp":" 947762399885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKAFU"," userResponse":" SAKAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762400261","data":{"timestamp":" 947762400260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762401215","data":{"timestamp":" 947762401214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" START_DIMBWI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762402742","data":{"timestamp":" 947762402741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762402957","data":{"timestamp":" 947762402957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762404767","data":{"timestamp":" 947762404767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762407009","data":{"timestamp":" 947762407008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762407851","data":{"timestamp":" 947762407850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762409355","data":{"timestamp":" 947762409354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762411228","data":{"timestamp":" 947762411228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762412985","data":{"timestamp":" 947762412985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762413956","data":{"timestamp":" 947762413955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKAFU"," userResponse":" SAKAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762414244","data":{"timestamp":" 947762414243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762414998","data":{"timestamp":" 947762414998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762415645","data":{"timestamp":" 947762415645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762416616","data":{"timestamp":" 947762416615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762417476","data":{"timestamp":" 947762417475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762418046","data":{"timestamp":" 947762418046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762420692","data":{"timestamp":" 947762420692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762424495","data":{"timestamp":" 947762424494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MNENE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762425552","data":{"timestamp":" 947762425552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MNENE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762427330","data":{"timestamp":" 947762427330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762428619","data":{"timestamp":" 947762428619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MNENE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762429431","data":{"timestamp":" 947762429431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNENE"," userResponse":" MNENE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762429753","data":{"timestamp":" 947762429753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762430638","data":{"timestamp":" 947762430638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762440259","data":{"timestamp":" 947762440259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762442212","data":{"timestamp":" 947762442210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762443130","data":{"timestamp":" 947762443128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762444094","data":{"timestamp":" 947762444093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNENE"," userResponse":" MNENE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762444775","data":{"timestamp":" 947762444774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762445303","data":{"timestamp":" 947762445302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762445891","data":{"timestamp":" 947762445890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762447968","data":{"timestamp":" 947762447967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762448562","data":{"timestamp":" 947762448562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" START_MWENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762449875","data":{"timestamp":" 947762449875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" MWENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762451164","data":{"timestamp":" 947762451164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762451467","data":{"timestamp":" 947762451466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762452376","data":{"timestamp":" 947762452376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBO"," userResponse":" UMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762452990","data":{"timestamp":" 947762452990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762453710","data":{"timestamp":" 947762453710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762456496","data":{"timestamp":" 947762456495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762457382","data":{"timestamp":" 947762457382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762458362","data":{"timestamp":" 947762458362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHAIFU"," userResponse":" DHAIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762459841","data":{"timestamp":" 947762459840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762460721","data":{"timestamp":" 947762460720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" MWENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762461731","data":{"timestamp":" 947762461730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762461999","data":{"timestamp":" 947762461998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762462526","data":{"timestamp":" 947762462526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBO"," userResponse":" UMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762463298","data":{"timestamp":" 947762463297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762463444","data":{"timestamp":" 947762463443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762464529","data":{"timestamp":" 947762464528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762465087","data":{"timestamp":" 947762465087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762465808","data":{"timestamp":" 947762465807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHAIFU"," userResponse":" DHAIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762471370","data":{"timestamp":" 947762471370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762471727","data":{"timestamp":" 947762471726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762471730","data":{"timestamp":" 947762471730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762472868","data":{"timestamp":" 947762472868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PAKATOKEA"," userResponse":" START_PAKATOKEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762474539","data":{"timestamp":" 947762474539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKATOKEA"," userResponse":" PAKATOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762475818","data":{"timestamp":" 947762475818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHORUBA"," userResponse":" DHORUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762477014","data":{"timestamp":" 947762477014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762478776","data":{"timestamp":" 947762478776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762480739","data":{"timestamp":" 947762480738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762481480","data":{"timestamp":" 947762481479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762481997","data":{"timestamp":" 947762481997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762483109","data":{"timestamp":" 947762483109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKATOKEA"," userResponse":" PAKATOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762484045","data":{"timestamp":" 947762484043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHORUBA"," userResponse":" DHORUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762484659","data":{"timestamp":" 947762484658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762488072","data":{"timestamp":" 947762488072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762488978","data":{"timestamp":" 947762488978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPIGA"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762491338","data":{"timestamp":" 947762491337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPIGA"," userResponse":" START_ILIPIGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762493053","data":{"timestamp":" 947762493053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPIGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762493838","data":{"timestamp":" 947762493837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KUPENYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762494964","data":{"timestamp":" 947762494964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762496324","data":{"timestamp":" 947762496323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762496622","data":{"timestamp":" 947762496622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENYA"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762500246","data":{"timestamp":" 947762500245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENYA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762501635","data":{"timestamp":" 947762501635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762503401","data":{"timestamp":" 947762503401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762503987","data":{"timestamp":" 947762503987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762504482","data":{"timestamp":" 947762504482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762505892","data":{"timestamp":" 947762505891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762507951","data":{"timestamp":" 947762507950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762508801","data":{"timestamp":" 947762508800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPIGA"," userResponse":" ILIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762509026","data":{"timestamp":" 947762509026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762509787","data":{"timestamp":" 947762509787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENYA"," userResponse":" KUPENYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762510348","data":{"timestamp":" 947762510347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762510961","data":{"timestamp":" 947762510961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762511171","data":{"timestamp":" 947762511171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762511804","data":{"timestamp":" 947762511802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762514504","data":{"timestamp":" 947762514503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762516921","data":{"timestamp":" 947762516921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAGAWIKA"," userResponse":" YAKAGAWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762517219","data":{"timestamp":" 947762517219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762517874","data":{"timestamp":" 947762517874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762518604","data":{"timestamp":" 947762518603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762519424","data":{"timestamp":" 947762519423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762522076","data":{"timestamp":" 947762522076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762524408","data":{"timestamp":" 947762524408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWEZA"," userResponse":" WAKAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762525189","data":{"timestamp":" 947762525189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762527079","data":{"timestamp":" 947762527079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762527093","data":{"timestamp":" 947762527093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762529986","data":{"timestamp":" 947762529986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" START_MFUPI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762533538","data":{"timestamp":" 947762533537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762535167","data":{"timestamp":" 947762535167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762537129","data":{"timestamp":" 947762537128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762538319","data":{"timestamp":" 947762538318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAGAWIKA"," userResponse":" YAKAGAWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762538626","data":{"timestamp":" 947762538626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762539101","data":{"timestamp":" 947762539100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762539836","data":{"timestamp":" 947762539835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762540669","data":{"timestamp":" 947762540668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762541268","data":{"timestamp":" 947762541268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762542068","data":{"timestamp":" 947762542068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWEZA"," userResponse":" WAKAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762542694","data":{"timestamp":" 947762542693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762543338","data":{"timestamp":" 947762543338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762543994","data":{"timestamp":" 947762543992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762544646","data":{"timestamp":" 947762544645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762547294","data":{"timestamp":" 947762547294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762547784","data":{"timestamp":" 947762547784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762548412","data":{"timestamp":" 947762548412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762549312","data":{"timestamp":" 947762549312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762550983","data":{"timestamp":" 947762550983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762551960","data":{"timestamp":" 947762551959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762552258","data":{"timestamp":" 947762552258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYENYE"," userResponse":" VYENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762552263","data":{"timestamp":" 947762552263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMBO"," userResponse":" MAUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762555177","data":{"timestamp":" 947762555177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762568786","data":{"timestamp":" 947762568786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762571036","data":{"timestamp":" 947762571035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762571585","data":{"timestamp":" 947762571585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762571905","data":{"timestamp":" 947762571904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762572547","data":{"timestamp":" 947762572546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762573197","data":{"timestamp":" 947762573196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762573456","data":{"timestamp":" 947762573456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762574024","data":{"timestamp":" 947762574023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYENYE"," userResponse":" VYENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762574747","data":{"timestamp":" 947762574745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMBO"," userResponse":" MAUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762575732","data":{"timestamp":" 947762575732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762576795","data":{"timestamp":" 947762576795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762579904","data":{"timestamp":" 947762579903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762581065","data":{"timestamp":" 947762581065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762581837","data":{"timestamp":" 947762581837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762583227","data":{"timestamp":" 947762583227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762583230","data":{"timestamp":" 947762583230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762584430","data":{"timestamp":" 947762584430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762585531","data":{"timestamp":" 947762585531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762587652","data":{"timestamp":" 947762587652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762588576","data":{"timestamp":" 947762588576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762589153","data":{"timestamp":" 947762589152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762589767","data":{"timestamp":" 947762589765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762590649","data":{"timestamp":" 947762590649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762592761","data":{"timestamp":" 947762592761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762593257","data":{"timestamp":" 947762593256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762594486","data":{"timestamp":" 947762594486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHOONA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762595595","data":{"timestamp":" 947762595595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHOONA"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762597322","data":{"timestamp":" 947762597322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHOONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762598095","data":{"timestamp":" 947762598095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHINI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762599033","data":{"timestamp":" 947762599032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHINI"," userResponse":" START_ARDHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762600632","data":{"timestamp":" 947762600631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762601403","data":{"timestamp":" 947762601403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILIVUTIA"," userResponse":" MAUMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762602845","data":{"timestamp":" 947762602844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILIVUTIA"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762604534","data":{"timestamp":" 947762604534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIVUTIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762606137","data":{"timestamp":" 947762606137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762609039","data":{"timestamp":" 947762609039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762610723","data":{"timestamp":" 947762610723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762611273","data":{"timestamp":" 947762611272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762612554","data":{"timestamp":" 947762612554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHOONA"," userResponse":" WALICHOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762613405","data":{"timestamp":" 947762613404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHINI"," userResponse":" ARDHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762614590","data":{"timestamp":" 947762614589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIVUTIA"," userResponse":" KILIVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762615186","data":{"timestamp":" 947762615185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762617520","data":{"timestamp":" 947762617520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762618867","data":{"timestamp":" 947762618867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762620545","data":{"timestamp":" 947762620544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762620713","data":{"timestamp":" 947762620713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762622499","data":{"timestamp":" 947762622499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762624365","data":{"timestamp":" 947762624365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPORUDIANA"," userResponse":" YALIPORUDIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762624954","data":{"timestamp":" 947762624954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" MAUMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762626109","data":{"timestamp":" 947762626108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762626600","data":{"timestamp":" 947762626600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762627201","data":{"timestamp":" 947762627201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762628854","data":{"timestamp":" 947762628854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762628858","data":{"timestamp":" 947762628858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762630999","data":{"timestamp":" 947762630999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762632485","data":{"timestamp":" 947762632485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" KUKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762633893","data":{"timestamp":" 947762633893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZURI"," userResponse":" UZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762635259","data":{"timestamp":" 947762635259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762637863","data":{"timestamp":" 947762637863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762639272","data":{"timestamp":" 947762639271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEONA"," userResponse":" WAMEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762641126","data":{"timestamp":" 947762641126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762641588","data":{"timestamp":" 947762641587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762643028","data":{"timestamp":" 947762643027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPORUDIANA"," userResponse":" YALIPORUDIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762643620","data":{"timestamp":" 947762643619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762644492","data":{"timestamp":" 947762644492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762645066","data":{"timestamp":" 947762645066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762646320","data":{"timestamp":" 947762646319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762647427","data":{"timestamp":" 947762647425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" KUKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762648202","data":{"timestamp":" 947762648201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZURI"," userResponse":" UZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762649266","data":{"timestamp":" 947762649266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762650185","data":{"timestamp":" 947762650184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEONA"," userResponse":" WAMEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762657658","data":{"timestamp":" 947762657658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATUWEZI"," userResponse":" START_HATUWEZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762658628","data":{"timestamp":" 947762658628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUWEZI"," userResponse":" HATUWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762662248","data":{"timestamp":" 947762662248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUENDELEA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762663712","data":{"timestamp":" 947762663711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUENDELEA"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762665515","data":{"timestamp":" 947762665515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUENDELEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762666292","data":{"timestamp":" 947762666291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762667926","data":{"timestamp":" 947762667926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762669017","data":{"timestamp":" 947762669016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762669808","data":{"timestamp":" 947762669807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762670394","data":{"timestamp":" 947762670394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762671610","data":{"timestamp":" 947762671610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" LENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762673078","data":{"timestamp":" 947762673077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762673978","data":{"timestamp":" 947762673978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LENYE"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762675451","data":{"timestamp":" 947762675451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LENYE"," userResponse":" LENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762676163","data":{"timestamp":" 947762676162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762676563","data":{"timestamp":" 947762676563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762677075","data":{"timestamp":" 947762677074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762679299","data":{"timestamp":" 947762679299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMBIANA"," userResponse":" START_WALIAMBIANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762681277","data":{"timestamp":" 947762681277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMBIANA"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762683235","data":{"timestamp":" 947762683235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMBIANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762684391","data":{"timestamp":" 947762684391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATUWEZI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762685488","data":{"timestamp":" 947762685488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUWEZI"," userResponse":" HATUWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762686443","data":{"timestamp":" 947762686443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUENDELEA"," userResponse":" KUENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762686604","data":{"timestamp":" 947762686603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762687039","data":{"timestamp":" 947762687039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762687135","data":{"timestamp":" 947762687134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762687563","data":{"timestamp":" 947762687562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762687595","data":{"timestamp":" 947762687595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LENYE"," userResponse":" LENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762687998","data":{"timestamp":" 947762687998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762688281","data":{"timestamp":" 947762688281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762688307","data":{"timestamp":" 947762688307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762689404","data":{"timestamp":" 947762689404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMBIANA"," userResponse":" WALIAMBIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762696308","data":{"timestamp":" 947762696308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762697082","data":{"timestamp":" 947762697082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762697095","data":{"timestamp":" 947762697095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762699125","data":{"timestamp":" 947762699124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUKAIONE"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762700300","data":{"timestamp":" 947762700300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUKAIONE"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762702001","data":{"timestamp":" 947762702000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKAIONE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762703396","data":{"timestamp":" 947762703395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" TUKAIONE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762704861","data":{"timestamp":" 947762704861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762706502","data":{"timestamp":" 947762706502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762706926","data":{"timestamp":" 947762706925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762707370","data":{"timestamp":" 947762707370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762708398","data":{"timestamp":" 947762708398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKAIONE"," userResponse":" TUKAIONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762709186","data":{"timestamp":" 947762709185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762712567","data":{"timestamp":" 947762712567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAWEZAJE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762713971","data":{"timestamp":" 947762713971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAWEZAJE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762715809","data":{"timestamp":" 947762715809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAWEZAJE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762717788","data":{"timestamp":" 947762717788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762717792","data":{"timestamp":" 947762717791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762719164","data":{"timestamp":" 947762719164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762720696","data":{"timestamp":" 947762720696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762723084","data":{"timestamp":" 947762723084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAWEZAJE"," userResponse":" TUTAWEZAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762723710","data":{"timestamp":" 947762723708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762724259","data":{"timestamp":" 947762724258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762725131","data":{"timestamp":" 947762725128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762727541","data":{"timestamp":" 947762727540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762728110","data":{"timestamp":" 947762728110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762728431","data":{"timestamp":" 947762728431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762729728","data":{"timestamp":" 947762729728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIULIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762731105","data":{"timestamp":" 947762731104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762733113","data":{"timestamp":" 947762733112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762734701","data":{"timestamp":" 947762734700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762735128","data":{"timestamp":" 947762735127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762735777","data":{"timestamp":" 947762735776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762736875","data":{"timestamp":" 947762736874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762738597","data":{"timestamp":" 947762738596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762739560","data":{"timestamp":" 947762739560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762741477","data":{"timestamp":" 947762741477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" MATUMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762743168","data":{"timestamp":" 947762743167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762743847","data":{"timestamp":" 947762743847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762744652","data":{"timestamp":" 947762744651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762745273","data":{"timestamp":" 947762745273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMBO"," userResponse":" MATUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762746905","data":{"timestamp":" 947762746904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762748694","data":{"timestamp":" 947762748693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" TUTATAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762748978","data":{"timestamp":" 947762748978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762750016","data":{"timestamp":" 947762750015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMBO"," userResponse":" MATUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762755022","data":{"timestamp":" 947762755022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762755026","data":{"timestamp":" 947762755025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762756607","data":{"timestamp":" 947762756607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762757951","data":{"timestamp":" 947762757950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762760797","data":{"timestamp":" 947762760797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762762878","data":{"timestamp":" 947762762877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762763656","data":{"timestamp":" 947762763656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762764593","data":{"timestamp":" 947762764593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762768188","data":{"timestamp":" 947762768188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUONA"," userResponse":" DUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762769435","data":{"timestamp":" 947762769435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUONA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMJIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762770918","data":{"timestamp":" 947762770917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762771913","data":{"timestamp":" 947762771912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" DUNI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762773335","data":{"timestamp":" 947762773334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNI"," userResponse":" DUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762773932","data":{"timestamp":" 947762773931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762774447","data":{"timestamp":" 947762774447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" DUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762775969","data":{"timestamp":" 947762775969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" DUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762777854","data":{"timestamp":" 947762777854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762778631","data":{"timestamp":" 947762778630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762779575","data":{"timestamp":" 947762779574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762779754","data":{"timestamp":" 947762779754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762779932","data":{"timestamp":" 947762779931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762780343","data":{"timestamp":" 947762780342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762780790","data":{"timestamp":" 947762780789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762780999","data":{"timestamp":" 947762780998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUONA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762781782","data":{"timestamp":" 947762781781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNI"," userResponse":" KUTUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762781891","data":{"timestamp":" 947762781891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" DUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762782416","data":{"timestamp":" 947762782415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762849069","data":{"timestamp":" 947762849068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762849166","data":{"timestamp":" 947762849166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d61f1f4e-4260-482b-8f23-41e8153b7baa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762890591","data":{"timestamp":" 947762890591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762893315","data":{"timestamp":" 947762893315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762895577","data":{"timestamp":" 947762895577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762898479","data":{"timestamp":" 947762898479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762901746","data":{"timestamp":" 947762901745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762905060","data":{"timestamp":" 947762905060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762912571","data":{"timestamp":" 947762912571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762916031","data":{"timestamp":" 947762916031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762917983","data":{"timestamp":" 947762917983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762938858","data":{"timestamp":" 947762938858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762941473","data":{"timestamp":" 947762941473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762944868","data":{"timestamp":" 947762944867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762956885","data":{"timestamp":" 947762956885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762960720","data":{"timestamp":" 947762960720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762963501","data":{"timestamp":" 947762963501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762966597","data":{"timestamp":" 947762966597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762968880","data":{"timestamp":" 947762968879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762978515","data":{"timestamp":" 947762978515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762986046","data":{"timestamp":" 947762986045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762988765","data":{"timestamp":" 947762988765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762991524","data":{"timestamp":" 947762991523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762997454","data":{"timestamp":" 947762997454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947762999464","data":{"timestamp":" 947762999463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763003726","data":{"timestamp":" 947763003726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763005958","data":{"timestamp":" 947763005958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763009242","data":{"timestamp":" 947763009242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763011295","data":{"timestamp":" 947763011295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763018224","data":{"timestamp":" 947763018224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763026138","data":{"timestamp":" 947763026138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763046885","data":{"timestamp":" 947763046885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763049871","data":{"timestamp":" 947763049871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763053224","data":{"timestamp":" 947763053224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763056298","data":{"timestamp":" 947763056298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763060389","data":{"timestamp":" 947763060389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763064069","data":{"timestamp":" 947763064069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763067081","data":{"timestamp":" 947763067081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763069563","data":{"timestamp":" 947763069563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763078357","data":{"timestamp":" 947763078357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763080126","data":{"timestamp":" 947763080126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763083134","data":{"timestamp":" 947763083134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763086007","data":{"timestamp":" 947763086007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763089800","data":{"timestamp":" 947763089800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763092452","data":{"timestamp":" 947763092452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763095573","data":{"timestamp":" 947763095573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763098317","data":{"timestamp":" 947763098317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763107124","data":{"timestamp":" 947763107124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763109017","data":{"timestamp":" 947763109016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763111545","data":{"timestamp":" 947763111545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763114018","data":{"timestamp":" 947763114018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763116781","data":{"timestamp":" 947763116781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763119002","data":{"timestamp":" 947763119001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763121458","data":{"timestamp":" 947763121458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763123887","data":{"timestamp":" 947763123886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763132651","data":{"timestamp":" 947763132650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763134588","data":{"timestamp":" 947763134588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763138164","data":{"timestamp":" 947763138164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763141144","data":{"timestamp":" 947763141144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763144437","data":{"timestamp":" 947763144437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763146807","data":{"timestamp":" 947763146807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763150146","data":{"timestamp":" 947763150146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763152135","data":{"timestamp":" 947763152135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763161278","data":{"timestamp":" 947763161278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763163298","data":{"timestamp":" 947763163298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763169714","data":{"timestamp":" 947763169714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763172140","data":{"timestamp":" 947763172140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763180449","data":{"timestamp":" 947763180449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763183035","data":{"timestamp":" 947763183035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763186282","data":{"timestamp":" 947763186282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763188835","data":{"timestamp":" 947763188835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763192056","data":{"timestamp":" 947763192056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763194263","data":{"timestamp":" 947763194262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763214875","data":{"timestamp":" 947763214875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763216981","data":{"timestamp":" 947763216981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763220548","data":{"timestamp":" 947763220548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763225661","data":{"timestamp":" 947763225660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763229074","data":{"timestamp":" 947763229074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763231735","data":{"timestamp":" 947763231735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763234677","data":{"timestamp":" 947763234677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763238943","data":{"timestamp":" 947763238943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763247424","data":{"timestamp":" 947763247424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763260015","data":{"timestamp":" 947763260015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763280936","data":{"timestamp":" 947763280936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763283215","data":{"timestamp":" 947763283215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763285119","data":{"timestamp":" 947763285119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763288427","data":{"timestamp":" 947763288427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763291209","data":{"timestamp":" 947763291209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763293121","data":{"timestamp":" 947763293121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763296060","data":{"timestamp":" 947763296060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763298808","data":{"timestamp":" 947763298808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763312631","data":{"timestamp":" 947763312630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 5acc546d-2070-4708-a0da-f997917d3399"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763329770","data":{"timestamp":" 947763329769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763329959","data":{"timestamp":" 947763329958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763330775","data":{"timestamp":" 947763330775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763331433","data":{"timestamp":" 947763331433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763332223","data":{"timestamp":" 947763332222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763332795","data":{"timestamp":" 947763332795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763333756","data":{"timestamp":" 947763333756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763334499","data":{"timestamp":" 947763334498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763335659","data":{"timestamp":" 947763335658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" INGAWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763336256","data":{"timestamp":" 947763336255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABIA"," userResponse":" TABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763336852","data":{"timestamp":" 947763336851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763337966","data":{"timestamp":" 947763337965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763338834","data":{"timestamp":" 947763338833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763339757","data":{"timestamp":" 947763339757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763340482","data":{"timestamp":" 947763340482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763340917","data":{"timestamp":" 947763340917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763341690","data":{"timestamp":" 947763341690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763344280","data":{"timestamp":" 947763344280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763345490","data":{"timestamp":" 947763345490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763347187","data":{"timestamp":" 947763347187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763350652","data":{"timestamp":" 947763350651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763352533","data":{"timestamp":" 947763352533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763355557","data":{"timestamp":" 947763355557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763357139","data":{"timestamp":" 947763357139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763358106","data":{"timestamp":" 947763358106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763359733","data":{"timestamp":" 947763359733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763360515","data":{"timestamp":" 947763360514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763360690","data":{"timestamp":" 947763360690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763362633","data":{"timestamp":" 947763362632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763363616","data":{"timestamp":" 947763363615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763363781","data":{"timestamp":" 947763363781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763365604","data":{"timestamp":" 947763365603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" INGAWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763366192","data":{"timestamp":" 947763366192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABIA"," userResponse":" TABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763366908","data":{"timestamp":" 947763366908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763367898","data":{"timestamp":" 947763367898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763368741","data":{"timestamp":" 947763368741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763370479","data":{"timestamp":" 947763370478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763370747","data":{"timestamp":" 947763370747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763373055","data":{"timestamp":" 947763373055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763375220","data":{"timestamp":" 947763375219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763376833","data":{"timestamp":" 947763376833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763377705","data":{"timestamp":" 947763377705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763379020","data":{"timestamp":" 947763379020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763380293","data":{"timestamp":" 947763380293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763382011","data":{"timestamp":" 947763382011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763384057","data":{"timestamp":" 947763384057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763384781","data":{"timestamp":" 947763384780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763385527","data":{"timestamp":" 947763385526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763386516","data":{"timestamp":" 947763386515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763386984","data":{"timestamp":" 947763386983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763387903","data":{"timestamp":" 947763387901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763389075","data":{"timestamp":" 947763389074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763389908","data":{"timestamp":" 947763389907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763390256","data":{"timestamp":" 947763390255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763393947","data":{"timestamp":" 947763393947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763394611","data":{"timestamp":" 947763394611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763396423","data":{"timestamp":" 947763396423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763397388","data":{"timestamp":" 947763397388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763399501","data":{"timestamp":" 947763399501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763401166","data":{"timestamp":" 947763401166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763402254","data":{"timestamp":" 947763402253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763403724","data":{"timestamp":" 947763403724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763405380","data":{"timestamp":" 947763405379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763406649","data":{"timestamp":" 947763406648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TABIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763408556","data":{"timestamp":" 947763408556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763408726","data":{"timestamp":" 947763408726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763410559","data":{"timestamp":" 947763410559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763411657","data":{"timestamp":" 947763411656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763414006","data":{"timestamp":" 947763414005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763414634","data":{"timestamp":" 947763414633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763415462","data":{"timestamp":" 947763415461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763416062","data":{"timestamp":" 947763416062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763416261","data":{"timestamp":" 947763416261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763416884","data":{"timestamp":" 947763416883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763418517","data":{"timestamp":" 947763418516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" KUMFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763419498","data":{"timestamp":" 947763419498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763420062","data":{"timestamp":" 947763420061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763420502","data":{"timestamp":" 947763420501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763422285","data":{"timestamp":" 947763422285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763422644","data":{"timestamp":" 947763422644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763423969","data":{"timestamp":" 947763423968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763424985","data":{"timestamp":" 947763424985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763424988","data":{"timestamp":" 947763424988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763425601","data":{"timestamp":" 947763425601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763426675","data":{"timestamp":" 947763426675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763429002","data":{"timestamp":" 947763429002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" START_KUMFAHAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763430678","data":{"timestamp":" 947763430678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763432458","data":{"timestamp":" 947763432458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763434153","data":{"timestamp":" 947763434153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763434282","data":{"timestamp":" 947763434282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763436625","data":{"timestamp":" 947763436624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763437273","data":{"timestamp":" 947763437272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763438352","data":{"timestamp":" 947763438351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763438808","data":{"timestamp":" 947763438807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763439597","data":{"timestamp":" 947763439597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEUPE"," userResponse":" CHEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763440467","data":{"timestamp":" 947763440467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" KILICHOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763440856","data":{"timestamp":" 947763440855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763440962","data":{"timestamp":" 947763440962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763441336","data":{"timestamp":" 947763441336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763442024","data":{"timestamp":" 947763442023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763442524","data":{"timestamp":" 947763442524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763442887","data":{"timestamp":" 947763442886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763443769","data":{"timestamp":" 947763443768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763445548","data":{"timestamp":" 947763445548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763446368","data":{"timestamp":" 947763446367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMWULIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763448360","data":{"timestamp":" 947763448359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763452754","data":{"timestamp":" 947763452754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763456751","data":{"timestamp":" 947763456751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763458343","data":{"timestamp":" 947763458343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763459832","data":{"timestamp":" 947763459831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763460888","data":{"timestamp":" 947763460887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEUPE"," userResponse":" CHEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763462105","data":{"timestamp":" 947763462105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763464001","data":{"timestamp":" 947763464000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763465942","data":{"timestamp":" 947763465942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763467202","data":{"timestamp":" 947763467202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763468099","data":{"timestamp":" 947763468099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763468422","data":{"timestamp":" 947763468422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763469024","data":{"timestamp":" 947763469024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763470616","data":{"timestamp":" 947763470616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763471396","data":{"timestamp":" 947763471395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763472093","data":{"timestamp":" 947763472092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763473211","data":{"timestamp":" 947763473211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763474616","data":{"timestamp":" 947763474616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763475209","data":{"timestamp":" 947763475208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763476139","data":{"timestamp":" 947763476139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763477015","data":{"timestamp":" 947763477014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763477775","data":{"timestamp":" 947763477774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763478674","data":{"timestamp":" 947763478674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INALIWA"," userResponse":" INALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763479723","data":{"timestamp":" 947763479722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763480664","data":{"timestamp":" 947763480663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPORUKA"," userResponse":" NINAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763481365","data":{"timestamp":" 947763481364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763483601","data":{"timestamp":" 947763483601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763484409","data":{"timestamp":" 947763484409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763484514","data":{"timestamp":" 947763484514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763485826","data":{"timestamp":" 947763485826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763488993","data":{"timestamp":" 947763488993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763491386","data":{"timestamp":" 947763491386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763492982","data":{"timestamp":" 947763492982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INALIWA"," userResponse":" INALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763493921","data":{"timestamp":" 947763493921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763495609","data":{"timestamp":" 947763495608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763497091","data":{"timestamp":" 947763497091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPORUKA"," userResponse":" NINAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763498100","data":{"timestamp":" 947763498099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" START_ANGANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763500388","data":{"timestamp":" 947763500388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763502527","data":{"timestamp":" 947763502525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763503586","data":{"timestamp":" 947763503585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAILA"," userResponse":" NINAILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763504594","data":{"timestamp":" 947763504593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763504961","data":{"timestamp":" 947763504960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763505690","data":{"timestamp":" 947763505689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763506732","data":{"timestamp":" 947763506731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763507303","data":{"timestamp":" 947763507303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763508787","data":{"timestamp":" 947763508787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" IMENIBANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763509669","data":{"timestamp":" 947763509669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763512936","data":{"timestamp":" 947763512936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763514342","data":{"timestamp":" 947763514342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAILA"," userResponse":" NINAILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763515436","data":{"timestamp":" 947763515435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763516348","data":{"timestamp":" 947763516348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763517025","data":{"timestamp":" 947763517025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" START_MREFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763518930","data":{"timestamp":" 947763518930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763520232","data":{"timestamp":" 947763520232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763521139","data":{"timestamp":" 947763521139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763522328","data":{"timestamp":" 947763522327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" START_IMENIBANDIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763523436","data":{"timestamp":" 947763523436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763525518","data":{"timestamp":" 947763525518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763526673","data":{"timestamp":" 947763526673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763529785","data":{"timestamp":" 947763529784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763530273","data":{"timestamp":" 947763530273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763530407","data":{"timestamp":" 947763530407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763531075","data":{"timestamp":" 947763531074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763532116","data":{"timestamp":" 947763532116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763533086","data":{"timestamp":" 947763533085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" ALITOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763533326","data":{"timestamp":" 947763533326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763533997","data":{"timestamp":" 947763533996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763534894","data":{"timestamp":" 947763534894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763535455","data":{"timestamp":" 947763535454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763535993","data":{"timestamp":" 947763535993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763536108","data":{"timestamp":" 947763536107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763536480","data":{"timestamp":" 947763536480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763536961","data":{"timestamp":" 947763536961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763540285","data":{"timestamp":" 947763540284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763541380","data":{"timestamp":" 947763541380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763542169","data":{"timestamp":" 947763542169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763542173","data":{"timestamp":" 947763542173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763543457","data":{"timestamp":" 947763543456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763545679","data":{"timestamp":" 947763545679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" START_ALITOKWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763548039","data":{"timestamp":" 947763548038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763549796","data":{"timestamp":" 947763549796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763550672","data":{"timestamp":" 947763550672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763551160","data":{"timestamp":" 947763551160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763552195","data":{"timestamp":" 947763552194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" START_KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763552965","data":{"timestamp":" 947763552964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" START_KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763554809","data":{"timestamp":" 947763554809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763555691","data":{"timestamp":" 947763555690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763556978","data":{"timestamp":" 947763556977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763558184","data":{"timestamp":" 947763558184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763559364","data":{"timestamp":" 947763559363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763560733","data":{"timestamp":" 947763560733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763561705","data":{"timestamp":" 947763561705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" ALITOKWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763563193","data":{"timestamp":" 947763563192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763563333","data":{"timestamp":" 947763563333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763565136","data":{"timestamp":" 947763565135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763566087","data":{"timestamp":" 947763566085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763566828","data":{"timestamp":" 947763566827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763567567","data":{"timestamp":" 947763567567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763568106","data":{"timestamp":" 947763568105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763568628","data":{"timestamp":" 947763568628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763570333","data":{"timestamp":" 947763570333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763571050","data":{"timestamp":" 947763571049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763572879","data":{"timestamp":" 947763572878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763574543","data":{"timestamp":" 947763574543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763575653","data":{"timestamp":" 947763575653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763576734","data":{"timestamp":" 947763576734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763577576","data":{"timestamp":" 947763577576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763579713","data":{"timestamp":" 947763579712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763581404","data":{"timestamp":" 947763581403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" ATAIPATAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763582124","data":{"timestamp":" 947763582123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763582563","data":{"timestamp":" 947763582561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763583446","data":{"timestamp":" 947763583446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763583978","data":{"timestamp":" 947763583977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763584526","data":{"timestamp":" 947763584524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763585056","data":{"timestamp":" 947763585056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763585257","data":{"timestamp":" 947763585256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763586350","data":{"timestamp":" 947763586350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" KUIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763587912","data":{"timestamp":" 947763587911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763588830","data":{"timestamp":" 947763588830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763590153","data":{"timestamp":" 947763590153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" ATAIPATAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763591738","data":{"timestamp":" 947763591737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763592864","data":{"timestamp":" 947763592864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763593979","data":{"timestamp":" 947763593979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" START_ANGANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763595712","data":{"timestamp":" 947763595712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763596927","data":{"timestamp":" 947763596927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763598041","data":{"timestamp":" 947763598041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763598457","data":{"timestamp":" 947763598456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763598938","data":{"timestamp":" 947763598938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763599230","data":{"timestamp":" 947763599230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" START_KUIRUKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763601923","data":{"timestamp":" 947763601923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" KUIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763604096","data":{"timestamp":" 947763604095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763604805","data":{"timestamp":" 947763604804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763605487","data":{"timestamp":" 947763605487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763606426","data":{"timestamp":" 947763606425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763607322","data":{"timestamp":" 947763607322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOPESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763608124","data":{"timestamp":" 947763608123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763608864","data":{"timestamp":" 947763608864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763609461","data":{"timestamp":" 947763609461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" NIWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763610824","data":{"timestamp":" 947763610823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763611577","data":{"timestamp":" 947763611576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763613614","data":{"timestamp":" 947763613614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" START_TAFADHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763614661","data":{"timestamp":" 947763614661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763616512","data":{"timestamp":" 947763616512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763618107","data":{"timestamp":" 947763618107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763618111","data":{"timestamp":" 947763618111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763619653","data":{"timestamp":" 947763619653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763621458","data":{"timestamp":" 947763621458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763623237","data":{"timestamp":" 947763623237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOPESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763624856","data":{"timestamp":" 947763624856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763625970","data":{"timestamp":" 947763625970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763627240","data":{"timestamp":" 947763627240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" START_NIWEZE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763628948","data":{"timestamp":" 947763628947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" NIWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763630457","data":{"timestamp":" 947763630457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" START_KUJITENGENEZEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763631545","data":{"timestamp":" 947763631545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763633653","data":{"timestamp":" 947763633652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763635023","data":{"timestamp":" 947763635023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763637046","data":{"timestamp":" 947763637045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763637530","data":{"timestamp":" 947763637529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763638478","data":{"timestamp":" 947763638477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763639374","data":{"timestamp":" 947763639374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763639956","data":{"timestamp":" 947763639955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763640503","data":{"timestamp":" 947763640502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763642505","data":{"timestamp":" 947763642505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763643031","data":{"timestamp":" 947763643030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763643401","data":{"timestamp":" 947763643401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763644700","data":{"timestamp":" 947763644700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763645102","data":{"timestamp":" 947763645101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763645621","data":{"timestamp":" 947763645620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763647738","data":{"timestamp":" 947763647738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763648465","data":{"timestamp":" 947763648464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763651899","data":{"timestamp":" 947763651899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763653021","data":{"timestamp":" 947763653021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763654803","data":{"timestamp":" 947763654803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763656357","data":{"timestamp":" 947763656356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763658736","data":{"timestamp":" 947763658735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763658925","data":{"timestamp":" 947763658925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763659709","data":{"timestamp":" 947763659708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" UKARIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763660133","data":{"timestamp":" 947763660133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763661216","data":{"timestamp":" 947763661215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763661704","data":{"timestamp":" 947763661703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763662424","data":{"timestamp":" 947763662423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763664478","data":{"timestamp":" 947763664478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763665166","data":{"timestamp":" 947763665165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763665580","data":{"timestamp":" 947763665580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" UKARIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763665590","data":{"timestamp":" 947763665590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763666778","data":{"timestamp":" 947763666778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763667181","data":{"timestamp":" 947763667180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763667899","data":{"timestamp":" 947763667898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763669654","data":{"timestamp":" 947763669654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763670886","data":{"timestamp":" 947763670885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYASHONA"," userResponse":" ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763671381","data":{"timestamp":" 947763671381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAWE"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763672000","data":{"timestamp":" 947763671999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763673729","data":{"timestamp":" 947763673728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763675008","data":{"timestamp":" 947763675007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYASHONA"," userResponse":" ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763675699","data":{"timestamp":" 947763675699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAWE"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763676132","data":{"timestamp":" 947763676131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763678774","data":{"timestamp":" 947763678773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763679050","data":{"timestamp":" 947763679050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763679561","data":{"timestamp":" 947763679561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763680123","data":{"timestamp":" 947763680123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763681428","data":{"timestamp":" 947763681427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763682109","data":{"timestamp":" 947763682109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763684781","data":{"timestamp":" 947763684781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763686613","data":{"timestamp":" 947763686612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763687343","data":{"timestamp":" 947763687342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763688410","data":{"timestamp":" 947763688410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763689798","data":{"timestamp":" 947763689797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763690570","data":{"timestamp":" 947763690570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" START_MANYOYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763692604","data":{"timestamp":" 947763692604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763693823","data":{"timestamp":" 947763693823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763695525","data":{"timestamp":" 947763695525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763696929","data":{"timestamp":" 947763696928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" START_AKAJARIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763698110","data":{"timestamp":" 947763698110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763699913","data":{"timestamp":" 947763699913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763701312","data":{"timestamp":" 947763701311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763703423","data":{"timestamp":" 947763703423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763705606","data":{"timestamp":" 947763705606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763706143","data":{"timestamp":" 947763706142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZITO"," userResponse":" UZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763706528","data":{"timestamp":" 947763706528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763707463","data":{"timestamp":" 947763707462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763709535","data":{"timestamp":" 947763709534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763710034","data":{"timestamp":" 947763710034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZITO"," userResponse":" UZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763710425","data":{"timestamp":" 947763710425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763710752","data":{"timestamp":" 947763710752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" START_ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763712407","data":{"timestamp":" 947763712407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" START_ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763714373","data":{"timestamp":" 947763714372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763715529","data":{"timestamp":" 947763715529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763716377","data":{"timestamp":" 947763716376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763717298","data":{"timestamp":" 947763717297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIBIDI"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763717505","data":{"timestamp":" 947763717505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFIKIRIE"," userResponse":" ILIBIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763718219","data":{"timestamp":" 947763718218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPANGO"," userResponse":" AFIKIRIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763718370","data":{"timestamp":" 947763718369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763729321","data":{"timestamp":" 947763729321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763729428","data":{"timestamp":" 947763729428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" edad7435-42bf-4ef9-87c3-add47bac3c89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763743708","data":{"timestamp":" 947763743707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763743903","data":{"timestamp":" 947763743902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763744723","data":{"timestamp":" 947763744723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763745379","data":{"timestamp":" 947763745379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763746168","data":{"timestamp":" 947763746168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763746736","data":{"timestamp":" 947763746735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763747697","data":{"timestamp":" 947763747697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763748438","data":{"timestamp":" 947763748437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763749600","data":{"timestamp":" 947763749598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" INGAWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763750192","data":{"timestamp":" 947763750191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABIA"," userResponse":" TABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763750793","data":{"timestamp":" 947763750792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763751908","data":{"timestamp":" 947763751907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763752781","data":{"timestamp":" 947763752780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763753707","data":{"timestamp":" 947763753706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763754451","data":{"timestamp":" 947763754450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763754902","data":{"timestamp":" 947763754902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763755678","data":{"timestamp":" 947763755677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763757560","data":{"timestamp":" 947763757560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763758511","data":{"timestamp":" 947763758511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763759081","data":{"timestamp":" 947763759081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763760629","data":{"timestamp":" 947763760628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763761704","data":{"timestamp":" 947763761703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763763285","data":{"timestamp":" 947763763285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763764440","data":{"timestamp":" 947763764440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763767343","data":{"timestamp":" 947763767343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763768532","data":{"timestamp":" 947763768532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763769585","data":{"timestamp":" 947763769585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" START_SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763771231","data":{"timestamp":" 947763771231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763772628","data":{"timestamp":" 947763772627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763774036","data":{"timestamp":" 947763774036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763775459","data":{"timestamp":" 947763775458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" START_INGAWAJE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763777331","data":{"timestamp":" 947763777331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" INGAWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763778892","data":{"timestamp":" 947763778892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABIA"," userResponse":" TABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763779131","data":{"timestamp":" 947763779131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763780559","data":{"timestamp":" 947763780559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763781520","data":{"timestamp":" 947763781519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763783236","data":{"timestamp":" 947763783235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763784828","data":{"timestamp":" 947763784828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763786511","data":{"timestamp":" 947763786510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763787629","data":{"timestamp":" 947763787629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763787927","data":{"timestamp":" 947763787927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763789044","data":{"timestamp":" 947763789044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763791089","data":{"timestamp":" 947763791088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763791827","data":{"timestamp":" 947763791826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763792576","data":{"timestamp":" 947763792575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763793568","data":{"timestamp":" 947763793567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763794035","data":{"timestamp":" 947763794034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763794954","data":{"timestamp":" 947763794954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763796122","data":{"timestamp":" 947763796122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763796955","data":{"timestamp":" 947763796955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763797304","data":{"timestamp":" 947763797304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763801371","data":{"timestamp":" 947763801371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763801376","data":{"timestamp":" 947763801376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763802129","data":{"timestamp":" 947763802129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763803377","data":{"timestamp":" 947763803376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763804670","data":{"timestamp":" 947763804669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763805053","data":{"timestamp":" 947763805053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" START_HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763807133","data":{"timestamp":" 947763807132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763808628","data":{"timestamp":" 947763808628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763810285","data":{"timestamp":" 947763810285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763811782","data":{"timestamp":" 947763811782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763814003","data":{"timestamp":" 947763814003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763815711","data":{"timestamp":" 947763815711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763818073","data":{"timestamp":" 947763818072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763818699","data":{"timestamp":" 947763818699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763819531","data":{"timestamp":" 947763819530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763820126","data":{"timestamp":" 947763820126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763820323","data":{"timestamp":" 947763820323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763820955","data":{"timestamp":" 947763820954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763822592","data":{"timestamp":" 947763822591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" KUMFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763823578","data":{"timestamp":" 947763823577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763824149","data":{"timestamp":" 947763824145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763824589","data":{"timestamp":" 947763824589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763827288","data":{"timestamp":" 947763827288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" START_ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763828405","data":{"timestamp":" 947763828404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763829328","data":{"timestamp":" 947763829327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" START_MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763830288","data":{"timestamp":" 947763830287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763831463","data":{"timestamp":" 947763831462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763832309","data":{"timestamp":" 947763832309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763834052","data":{"timestamp":" 947763834051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763843034","data":{"timestamp":" 947763843033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763845580","data":{"timestamp":" 947763845580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763846598","data":{"timestamp":" 947763846598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763848138","data":{"timestamp":" 947763848137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763849360","data":{"timestamp":" 947763849359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763851067","data":{"timestamp":" 947763851066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763851527","data":{"timestamp":" 947763851527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763852433","data":{"timestamp":" 947763852433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763853508","data":{"timestamp":" 947763853508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763854119","data":{"timestamp":" 947763854119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763856412","data":{"timestamp":" 947763856412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763857063","data":{"timestamp":" 947763857062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763858142","data":{"timestamp":" 947763858141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763858600","data":{"timestamp":" 947763858599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763859392","data":{"timestamp":" 947763859392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEUPE"," userResponse":" CHEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763860266","data":{"timestamp":" 947763860265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" KILICHOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763860655","data":{"timestamp":" 947763860654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763860768","data":{"timestamp":" 947763860767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763861147","data":{"timestamp":" 947763861147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763861830","data":{"timestamp":" 947763861829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763862332","data":{"timestamp":" 947763862331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763862693","data":{"timestamp":" 947763862692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763863576","data":{"timestamp":" 947763863576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763866436","data":{"timestamp":" 947763866436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763867442","data":{"timestamp":" 947763867442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMWULIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763869529","data":{"timestamp":" 947763869528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763875889","data":{"timestamp":" 947763875889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763880325","data":{"timestamp":" 947763880325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763881215","data":{"timestamp":" 947763881215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763882516","data":{"timestamp":" 947763882516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEUPE"," userResponse":" CHEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763884183","data":{"timestamp":" 947763884183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" KILICHOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763884768","data":{"timestamp":" 947763884768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763885594","data":{"timestamp":" 947763885594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763886001","data":{"timestamp":" 947763886001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763886309","data":{"timestamp":" 947763886309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763886976","data":{"timestamp":" 947763886976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763887413","data":{"timestamp":" 947763887413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763888805","data":{"timestamp":" 947763888804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763890229","data":{"timestamp":" 947763890228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763890820","data":{"timestamp":" 947763890819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763891749","data":{"timestamp":" 947763891748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763892618","data":{"timestamp":" 947763892618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763893377","data":{"timestamp":" 947763893376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763894288","data":{"timestamp":" 947763894287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INALIWA"," userResponse":" INALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763895340","data":{"timestamp":" 947763895339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763896281","data":{"timestamp":" 947763896280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPORUKA"," userResponse":" NINAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763896971","data":{"timestamp":" 947763896971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763898892","data":{"timestamp":" 947763898892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763898895","data":{"timestamp":" 947763898895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763899597","data":{"timestamp":" 947763899597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763900493","data":{"timestamp":" 947763900492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763901148","data":{"timestamp":" 947763901147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763901972","data":{"timestamp":" 947763901971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INALIWA"," userResponse":" INALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763902891","data":{"timestamp":" 947763902891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763903502","data":{"timestamp":" 947763903502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPORUKA"," userResponse":" NINAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763904476","data":{"timestamp":" 947763904476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763906604","data":{"timestamp":" 947763906603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763907660","data":{"timestamp":" 947763907659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAILA"," userResponse":" NINAILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763908664","data":{"timestamp":" 947763908664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763909032","data":{"timestamp":" 947763909031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763909764","data":{"timestamp":" 947763909763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763910805","data":{"timestamp":" 947763910804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763911376","data":{"timestamp":" 947763911375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763912860","data":{"timestamp":" 947763912859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" IMENIBANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763913741","data":{"timestamp":" 947763913740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763916443","data":{"timestamp":" 947763916443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763917025","data":{"timestamp":" 947763917025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAILA"," userResponse":" NINAILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763918819","data":{"timestamp":" 947763918819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763918822","data":{"timestamp":" 947763918822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763919226","data":{"timestamp":" 947763919226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763920308","data":{"timestamp":" 947763920308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763920511","data":{"timestamp":" 947763920511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763921844","data":{"timestamp":" 947763921844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" START_IMENIBANDIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763923107","data":{"timestamp":" 947763923107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763925213","data":{"timestamp":" 947763925213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763926604","data":{"timestamp":" 947763926604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763929709","data":{"timestamp":" 947763929708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763930194","data":{"timestamp":" 947763930194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763930330","data":{"timestamp":" 947763930330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763931001","data":{"timestamp":" 947763931000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763932044","data":{"timestamp":" 947763932043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763933020","data":{"timestamp":" 947763933020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" ALITOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763933260","data":{"timestamp":" 947763933259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763933931","data":{"timestamp":" 947763933931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763934834","data":{"timestamp":" 947763934834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763935399","data":{"timestamp":" 947763935398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763935938","data":{"timestamp":" 947763935938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763936053","data":{"timestamp":" 947763936053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763936422","data":{"timestamp":" 947763936422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763936903","data":{"timestamp":" 947763936902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763943674","data":{"timestamp":" 947763943673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763946446","data":{"timestamp":" 947763946445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763949096","data":{"timestamp":" 947763949096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763950222","data":{"timestamp":" 947763950222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763950697","data":{"timestamp":" 947763950697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763952735","data":{"timestamp":" 947763952734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763954150","data":{"timestamp":" 947763954150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763955108","data":{"timestamp":" 947763955108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" START_ALITOKWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763956828","data":{"timestamp":" 947763956827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763957490","data":{"timestamp":" 947763957490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763958408","data":{"timestamp":" 947763958408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763959999","data":{"timestamp":" 947763959998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" START_KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763961687","data":{"timestamp":" 947763961687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763963167","data":{"timestamp":" 947763963167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763964466","data":{"timestamp":" 947763964466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763964473","data":{"timestamp":" 947763964473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763964976","data":{"timestamp":" 947763964975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763965403","data":{"timestamp":" 947763965402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763967209","data":{"timestamp":" 947763967208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763968156","data":{"timestamp":" 947763968155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763968897","data":{"timestamp":" 947763968897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763969636","data":{"timestamp":" 947763969635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763970173","data":{"timestamp":" 947763970172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763970700","data":{"timestamp":" 947763970699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763973220","data":{"timestamp":" 947763973220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763974009","data":{"timestamp":" 947763974009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763974846","data":{"timestamp":" 947763974846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763976947","data":{"timestamp":" 947763976946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763978015","data":{"timestamp":" 947763978014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763979323","data":{"timestamp":" 947763979322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763980399","data":{"timestamp":" 947763980399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763981711","data":{"timestamp":" 947763981711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763983860","data":{"timestamp":" 947763983859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763985547","data":{"timestamp":" 947763985546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" ATAIPATAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763986272","data":{"timestamp":" 947763986272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763986710","data":{"timestamp":" 947763986709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763987597","data":{"timestamp":" 947763987596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763988128","data":{"timestamp":" 947763988128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763988674","data":{"timestamp":" 947763988673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763989201","data":{"timestamp":" 947763989200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763989398","data":{"timestamp":" 947763989398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763990491","data":{"timestamp":" 947763990490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" KUIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763992706","data":{"timestamp":" 947763992706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763993806","data":{"timestamp":" 947763993806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" ATAIPATAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763994795","data":{"timestamp":" 947763994795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763994912","data":{"timestamp":" 947763994912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763996097","data":{"timestamp":" 947763996097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763997493","data":{"timestamp":" 947763997492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947763998864","data":{"timestamp":" 947763998864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764001678","data":{"timestamp":" 947764001678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764003504","data":{"timestamp":" 947764003504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764003509","data":{"timestamp":" 947764003509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764004020","data":{"timestamp":" 947764004020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764004790","data":{"timestamp":" 947764004790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764005228","data":{"timestamp":" 947764005227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" KUIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764007425","data":{"timestamp":" 947764007424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764008136","data":{"timestamp":" 947764008135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764008841","data":{"timestamp":" 947764008841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764009782","data":{"timestamp":" 947764009781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764010673","data":{"timestamp":" 947764010673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOPESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764011477","data":{"timestamp":" 947764011476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764012219","data":{"timestamp":" 947764012218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764012821","data":{"timestamp":" 947764012820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" NIWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764014184","data":{"timestamp":" 947764014183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764014935","data":{"timestamp":" 947764014934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764020064","data":{"timestamp":" 947764020064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764021652","data":{"timestamp":" 947764021652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764022317","data":{"timestamp":" 947764022317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" START_ALITAMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764024418","data":{"timestamp":" 947764024418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764026042","data":{"timestamp":" 947764026041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764028036","data":{"timestamp":" 947764028036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764029503","data":{"timestamp":" 947764029502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764031773","data":{"timestamp":" 947764031773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOPESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764032674","data":{"timestamp":" 947764032673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" START_MANYOYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764034775","data":{"timestamp":" 947764034775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764036086","data":{"timestamp":" 947764036086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764037222","data":{"timestamp":" 947764037222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764039520","data":{"timestamp":" 947764039520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764041311","data":{"timestamp":" 947764041310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764043364","data":{"timestamp":" 947764043363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" NIWEZE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764045856","data":{"timestamp":" 947764045856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764046645","data":{"timestamp":" 947764046645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764048662","data":{"timestamp":" 947764048661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764049149","data":{"timestamp":" 947764049148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764050098","data":{"timestamp":" 947764050098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764050984","data":{"timestamp":" 947764050984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764051565","data":{"timestamp":" 947764051564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764052114","data":{"timestamp":" 947764052113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764054641","data":{"timestamp":" 947764054641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764056192","data":{"timestamp":" 947764056192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764056719","data":{"timestamp":" 947764056719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764057227","data":{"timestamp":" 947764057227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764058817","data":{"timestamp":" 947764058817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764058829","data":{"timestamp":" 947764058828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764058943","data":{"timestamp":" 947764058943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764061094","data":{"timestamp":" 947764061093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764061826","data":{"timestamp":" 947764061826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764063872","data":{"timestamp":" 947764063872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764064846","data":{"timestamp":" 947764064846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764076932","data":{"timestamp":" 947764076932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764078515","data":{"timestamp":" 947764078514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764080911","data":{"timestamp":" 947764080910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764081108","data":{"timestamp":" 947764081107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764081890","data":{"timestamp":" 947764081889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" UKARIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764082326","data":{"timestamp":" 947764082326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764083407","data":{"timestamp":" 947764083406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764083899","data":{"timestamp":" 947764083899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764084620","data":{"timestamp":" 947764084618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764088722","data":{"timestamp":" 947764088721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764090379","data":{"timestamp":" 947764090378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764090392","data":{"timestamp":" 947764090391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764091573","data":{"timestamp":" 947764091572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764093930","data":{"timestamp":" 947764093930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" START_UKARIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764095523","data":{"timestamp":" 947764095523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764097305","data":{"timestamp":" 947764097305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764097407","data":{"timestamp":" 947764097407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764098711","data":{"timestamp":" 947764098711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764099405","data":{"timestamp":" 947764099405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764100051","data":{"timestamp":" 947764100050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764101828","data":{"timestamp":" 947764101827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764103062","data":{"timestamp":" 947764103061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYASHONA"," userResponse":" ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764103562","data":{"timestamp":" 947764103561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAWE"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764104182","data":{"timestamp":" 947764104182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764105905","data":{"timestamp":" 947764105904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764106692","data":{"timestamp":" 947764106692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYASHONA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764108516","data":{"timestamp":" 947764108516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYASHONA"," userResponse":" ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764109587","data":{"timestamp":" 947764109587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAWE"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764110092","data":{"timestamp":" 947764110091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764112738","data":{"timestamp":" 947764112737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764113017","data":{"timestamp":" 947764113016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764113525","data":{"timestamp":" 947764113524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764114084","data":{"timestamp":" 947764114083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764115384","data":{"timestamp":" 947764115384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764116075","data":{"timestamp":" 947764116074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764118127","data":{"timestamp":" 947764118126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" START_AKAYAUNGANISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764119151","data":{"timestamp":" 947764119150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764121235","data":{"timestamp":" 947764121234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764122026","data":{"timestamp":" 947764122025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764123066","data":{"timestamp":" 947764123066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764123897","data":{"timestamp":" 947764123897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764123903","data":{"timestamp":" 947764123903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764125464","data":{"timestamp":" 947764125464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764128830","data":{"timestamp":" 947764128830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764130616","data":{"timestamp":" 947764130615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764131985","data":{"timestamp":" 947764131985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764133713","data":{"timestamp":" 947764133713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764135297","data":{"timestamp":" 947764135297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764137478","data":{"timestamp":" 947764137477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764138015","data":{"timestamp":" 947764138015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZITO"," userResponse":" UZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764138401","data":{"timestamp":" 947764138401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764139330","data":{"timestamp":" 947764139330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764145202","data":{"timestamp":" 947764145202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764146649","data":{"timestamp":" 947764146648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZITO"," userResponse":" UZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764148011","data":{"timestamp":" 947764148011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764150047","data":{"timestamp":" 947764150047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764152995","data":{"timestamp":" 947764152994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764154986","data":{"timestamp":" 947764154985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764155910","data":{"timestamp":" 947764155909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIBIDI"," userResponse":" ILIBIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764156782","data":{"timestamp":" 947764156782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFIKIRIE"," userResponse":" AFIKIRIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764157376","data":{"timestamp":" 947764157375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPANGO"," userResponse":" MPANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764157998","data":{"timestamp":" 947764157998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764159469","data":{"timestamp":" 947764159469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764160572","data":{"timestamp":" 947764160572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIBIDI"," userResponse":" ILIBIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764161648","data":{"timestamp":" 947764161648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFIKIRIE"," userResponse":" AFIKIRIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764162467","data":{"timestamp":" 947764162466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPANGO"," userResponse":" MPANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764163477","data":{"timestamp":" 947764163476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764166652","data":{"timestamp":" 947764166651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764167372","data":{"timestamp":" 947764167371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764167790","data":{"timestamp":" 947764167789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764168842","data":{"timestamp":" 947764168842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764169923","data":{"timestamp":" 947764169922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUSHIKE"," userResponse":" NIKUSHIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764170073","data":{"timestamp":" 947764170073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764170706","data":{"timestamp":" 947764170705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764171339","data":{"timestamp":" 947764171338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764172754","data":{"timestamp":" 947764172753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKAPORUKA"," userResponse":" UTAKAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764173711","data":{"timestamp":" 947764173710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764176657","data":{"timestamp":" 947764176657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764179474","data":{"timestamp":" 947764179474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" START_TAFADHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764181372","data":{"timestamp":" 947764181372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764182456","data":{"timestamp":" 947764182456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764183159","data":{"timestamp":" 947764183158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764184641","data":{"timestamp":" 947764184641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" START_TAFADHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764185758","data":{"timestamp":" 947764185757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764188148","data":{"timestamp":" 947764188148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUSHIKE"," userResponse":" NIKUSHIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764189059","data":{"timestamp":" 947764189058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764189425","data":{"timestamp":" 947764189425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764190658","data":{"timestamp":" 947764190658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764193550","data":{"timestamp":" 947764193549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKAPORUKA"," userResponse":" START_UTAKAPORUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764197491","data":{"timestamp":" 947764197491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKAPORUKA"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764199343","data":{"timestamp":" 947764199343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKAPORUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764200628","data":{"timestamp":" 947764200628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764202751","data":{"timestamp":" 947764202749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764203481","data":{"timestamp":" 947764203481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764207045","data":{"timestamp":" 947764207045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764208067","data":{"timestamp":" 947764208067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764213938","data":{"timestamp":" 947764213937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764215659","data":{"timestamp":" 947764215659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764216204","data":{"timestamp":" 947764216203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764217359","data":{"timestamp":" 947764217358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUBALI"," userResponse":" AKAKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764217998","data":{"timestamp":" 947764217997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764221096","data":{"timestamp":" 947764221096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764223411","data":{"timestamp":" 947764223410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764224951","data":{"timestamp":" 947764224950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764227340","data":{"timestamp":" 947764227339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764231236","data":{"timestamp":" 947764231236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" START_SAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764232779","data":{"timestamp":" 947764232779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764235265","data":{"timestamp":" 947764235265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUBALI"," userResponse":" START_SAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764238059","data":{"timestamp":" 947764238058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUBALI"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764240080","data":{"timestamp":" 947764240079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUBALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764242792","data":{"timestamp":" 947764242791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764248189","data":{"timestamp":" 947764248189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764250554","data":{"timestamp":" 947764250553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764250941","data":{"timestamp":" 947764250940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764251428","data":{"timestamp":" 947764251427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764252117","data":{"timestamp":" 947764252116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764254552","data":{"timestamp":" 947764254552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764255258","data":{"timestamp":" 947764255258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764256367","data":{"timestamp":" 947764256366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764256463","data":{"timestamp":" 947764256463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764258160","data":{"timestamp":" 947764258159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764258790","data":{"timestamp":" 947764258789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUFANYE"," userResponse":" TUFANYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764259237","data":{"timestamp":" 947764259237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764260099","data":{"timestamp":" 947764260098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764261866","data":{"timestamp":" 947764261866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764262341","data":{"timestamp":" 947764262341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUFANYE"," userResponse":" TUFANYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764262779","data":{"timestamp":" 947764262779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764263775","data":{"timestamp":" 947764263775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764266518","data":{"timestamp":" 947764266517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUCHA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764266959","data":{"timestamp":" 947764266959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764267633","data":{"timestamp":" 947764267633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764268652","data":{"timestamp":" 947764268651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764269582","data":{"timestamp":" 947764269582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIMSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764269984","data":{"timestamp":" 947764269983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764270586","data":{"timestamp":" 947764270586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764271096","data":{"timestamp":" 947764271096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764271638","data":{"timestamp":" 947764271637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764272470","data":{"timestamp":" 947764272469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764273152","data":{"timestamp":" 947764273152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764273906","data":{"timestamp":" 947764273905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AKARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764274729","data":{"timestamp":" 947764274729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764278598","data":{"timestamp":" 947764278597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUCHA"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764279389","data":{"timestamp":" 947764279389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUCHA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764281274","data":{"timestamp":" 947764281273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUCHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764282167","data":{"timestamp":" 947764282167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764283829","data":{"timestamp":" 947764283828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764285513","data":{"timestamp":" 947764285513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764287836","data":{"timestamp":" 947764287835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIMSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764288828","data":{"timestamp":" 947764288828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764295191","data":{"timestamp":" 947764295190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764296455","data":{"timestamp":" 947764296455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764297653","data":{"timestamp":" 947764297652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764299367","data":{"timestamp":" 947764299367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764301364","data":{"timestamp":" 947764301364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764302870","data":{"timestamp":" 947764302870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764303598","data":{"timestamp":" 947764303598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764305133","data":{"timestamp":" 947764305133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764306969","data":{"timestamp":" 947764306968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764307751","data":{"timestamp":" 947764307750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764310179","data":{"timestamp":" 947764310178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764312545","data":{"timestamp":" 947764312544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764313344","data":{"timestamp":" 947764313343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764314451","data":{"timestamp":" 947764314450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAMANI"," userResponse":" AKITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764315048","data":{"timestamp":" 947764315047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764315930","data":{"timestamp":" 947764315930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764316862","data":{"timestamp":" 947764316861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764317776","data":{"timestamp":" 947764317775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764318530","data":{"timestamp":" 947764318529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764319443","data":{"timestamp":" 947764319442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKWA"," userResponse":" AKATOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764319605","data":{"timestamp":" 947764319604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764320308","data":{"timestamp":" 947764320308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764320809","data":{"timestamp":" 947764320808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764324075","data":{"timestamp":" 947764324075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764325005","data":{"timestamp":" 947764325005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764326703","data":{"timestamp":" 947764326702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764329214","data":{"timestamp":" 947764329214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764331173","data":{"timestamp":" 947764331172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764332960","data":{"timestamp":" 947764332960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764335841","data":{"timestamp":" 947764335841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAMANI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764336609","data":{"timestamp":" 947764336608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAMANI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764338348","data":{"timestamp":" 947764338348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAMANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764342810","data":{"timestamp":" 947764342809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" START_AKATOKWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764344644","data":{"timestamp":" 947764344643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764347765","data":{"timestamp":" 947764347764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ILIYOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764349274","data":{"timestamp":" 947764349274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764350820","data":{"timestamp":" 947764350819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764352413","data":{"timestamp":" 947764352412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764353321","data":{"timestamp":" 947764353320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764356984","data":{"timestamp":" 947764356983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKWA"," userResponse":" AKATOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764357816","data":{"timestamp":" 947764357815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764358620","data":{"timestamp":" 947764358620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764359964","data":{"timestamp":" 947764359964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764361820","data":{"timestamp":" 947764361820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764363089","data":{"timestamp":" 947764363087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764363718","data":{"timestamp":" 947764363716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764364748","data":{"timestamp":" 947764364747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764365820","data":{"timestamp":" 947764365820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764366992","data":{"timestamp":" 947764366991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHOKA"," userResponse":" AKACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764367655","data":{"timestamp":" 947764367654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764372749","data":{"timestamp":" 947764372748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764376249","data":{"timestamp":" 947764376248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIRUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764379174","data":{"timestamp":" 947764379174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764381074","data":{"timestamp":" 947764381074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764383481","data":{"timestamp":" 947764383481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764384958","data":{"timestamp":" 947764384958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764386874","data":{"timestamp":" 947764386874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHOKA"," userResponse":" AKACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764386982","data":{"timestamp":" 947764386982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" START_KABISA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764389132","data":{"timestamp":" 947764389131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764391258","data":{"timestamp":" 947764391258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764391762","data":{"timestamp":" 947764391762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764392750","data":{"timestamp":" 947764392749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOMBA"," userResponse":" AKAMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764394161","data":{"timestamp":" 947764394159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDELEA"," userResponse":" ENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764394920","data":{"timestamp":" 947764394920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764395257","data":{"timestamp":" 947764395257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764396028","data":{"timestamp":" 947764396027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764396415","data":{"timestamp":" 947764396414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764400082","data":{"timestamp":" 947764400081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764404023","data":{"timestamp":" 947764404023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" ENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764405586","data":{"timestamp":" 947764405586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764406741","data":{"timestamp":" 947764406740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764408096","data":{"timestamp":" 947764408096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764410180","data":{"timestamp":" 947764410180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOMBA"," userResponse":" START_AKAMWOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764411754","data":{"timestamp":" 947764411754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOMBA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764413706","data":{"timestamp":" 947764413706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764414778","data":{"timestamp":" 947764414778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDELEA"," userResponse":" ENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764415503","data":{"timestamp":" 947764415502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764417472","data":{"timestamp":" 947764417472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764420662","data":{"timestamp":" 947764420662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764422695","data":{"timestamp":" 947764422695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" START_ALIRUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764424476","data":{"timestamp":" 947764424476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764427488","data":{"timestamp":" 947764427487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764428310","data":{"timestamp":" 947764428309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPANDE"," userResponse":" KIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764428637","data":{"timestamp":" 947764428636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764429317","data":{"timestamp":" 947764429317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764429862","data":{"timestamp":" 947764429861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764430339","data":{"timestamp":" 947764430339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764431013","data":{"timestamp":" 947764431013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764431897","data":{"timestamp":" 947764431897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764432882","data":{"timestamp":" 947764432882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764434106","data":{"timestamp":" 947764434106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764438401","data":{"timestamp":" 947764438400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764444838","data":{"timestamp":" 947764444838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764446034","data":{"timestamp":" 947764446034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPANDE"," userResponse":" KIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764446352","data":{"timestamp":" 947764446352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764448668","data":{"timestamp":" 947764448668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764449656","data":{"timestamp":" 947764449656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764450041","data":{"timestamp":" 947764450041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764450666","data":{"timestamp":" 947764450666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764452465","data":{"timestamp":" 947764452465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764454182","data":{"timestamp":" 947764454181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764462613","data":{"timestamp":" 947764462613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" START_ALISIKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764464664","data":{"timestamp":" 947764464664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764466521","data":{"timestamp":" 947764466520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764468517","data":{"timestamp":" 947764468517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYOYA"," userResponse":" UNYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764469284","data":{"timestamp":" 947764469283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764470613","data":{"timestamp":" 947764470612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIOUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764471795","data":{"timestamp":" 947764471794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATOKA"," userResponse":" UKATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764472455","data":{"timestamp":" 947764472454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764472706","data":{"timestamp":" 947764472706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764473441","data":{"timestamp":" 947764473440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764475489","data":{"timestamp":" 947764475488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYOYA"," userResponse":" UNYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764476472","data":{"timestamp":" 947764476472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764477082","data":{"timestamp":" 947764477082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIOUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764478082","data":{"timestamp":" 947764478081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UKATOKA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764479316","data":{"timestamp":" 947764479316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UKATOKA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764481049","data":{"timestamp":" 947764481048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764481357","data":{"timestamp":" 947764481357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764482161","data":{"timestamp":" 947764482160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764482378","data":{"timestamp":" 947764482378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764489249","data":{"timestamp":" 947764489248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764490946","data":{"timestamp":" 947764490945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764491832","data":{"timestamp":" 947764491832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764492476","data":{"timestamp":" 947764492476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764493178","data":{"timestamp":" 947764493178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764493365","data":{"timestamp":" 947764493364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764493889","data":{"timestamp":" 947764493889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764496366","data":{"timestamp":" 947764496366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764496775","data":{"timestamp":" 947764496775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764497346","data":{"timestamp":" 947764497346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764497954","data":{"timestamp":" 947764497954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764497960","data":{"timestamp":" 947764497960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764498616","data":{"timestamp":" 947764498616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764500497","data":{"timestamp":" 947764500496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764501862","data":{"timestamp":" 947764501862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIJISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764502973","data":{"timestamp":" 947764502972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEONDOLEWA"," userResponse":" AMEONDOLEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764503688","data":{"timestamp":" 947764503687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764504471","data":{"timestamp":" 947764504470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZIGO"," userResponse":" MZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764504700","data":{"timestamp":" 947764504699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764505327","data":{"timestamp":" 947764505327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764505829","data":{"timestamp":" 947764505828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764506701","data":{"timestamp":" 947764506701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAPONA"," userResponse":" UKAPONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764511127","data":{"timestamp":" 947764511127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764512293","data":{"timestamp":" 947764512293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764515261","data":{"timestamp":" 947764515261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJISIKIA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764516270","data":{"timestamp":" 947764516270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJISIKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764518132","data":{"timestamp":" 947764518132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJISIKIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764521932","data":{"timestamp":" 947764521932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEONDOLEWA"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764523798","data":{"timestamp":" 947764523798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEONDOLEWA"," userResponse":" START_AMEONDOLEWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764525708","data":{"timestamp":" 947764525707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEONDOLEWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764526432","data":{"timestamp":" 947764526432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764527873","data":{"timestamp":" 947764527873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZIGO"," userResponse":" MZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764527877","data":{"timestamp":" 947764527877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764529387","data":{"timestamp":" 947764529387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764530879","data":{"timestamp":" 947764530879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764533966","data":{"timestamp":" 947764533965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UKAPONA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764535506","data":{"timestamp":" 947764535506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAPONA"," userResponse":" UKAPONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764537552","data":{"timestamp":" 947764537552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764539324","data":{"timestamp":" 947764539323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764539388","data":{"timestamp":" 947764539388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764540491","data":{"timestamp":" 947764540490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764541932","data":{"timestamp":" 947764541931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764543674","data":{"timestamp":" 947764543674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764545091","data":{"timestamp":" 947764545091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" START_ALIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764546679","data":{"timestamp":" 947764546678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764546852","data":{"timestamp":" 947764546852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764546861","data":{"timestamp":" 947764546861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764548933","data":{"timestamp":" 947764548933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764551571","data":{"timestamp":" 947764551571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764553342","data":{"timestamp":" 947764553342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764553800","data":{"timestamp":" 947764553799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764554862","data":{"timestamp":" 947764554861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764556056","data":{"timestamp":" 947764556055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764558356","data":{"timestamp":" 947764558355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764558867","data":{"timestamp":" 947764558866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764560622","data":{"timestamp":" 947764560622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764560961","data":{"timestamp":" 947764560961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764562958","data":{"timestamp":" 947764562957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764564209","data":{"timestamp":" 947764564209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITIKIA"," userResponse":" KUITIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764565070","data":{"timestamp":" 947764565069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764565921","data":{"timestamp":" 947764565920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764566857","data":{"timestamp":" 947764566855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYUME"," userResponse":" KINYUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764568441","data":{"timestamp":" 947764568441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764568575","data":{"timestamp":" 947764568575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764569563","data":{"timestamp":" 947764569563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764570678","data":{"timestamp":" 947764570678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764572922","data":{"timestamp":" 947764572921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764574955","data":{"timestamp":" 947764574955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764576050","data":{"timestamp":" 947764576050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITIKIA"," userResponse":" KUITIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764577151","data":{"timestamp":" 947764577151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764578273","data":{"timestamp":" 947764578272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764578968","data":{"timestamp":" 947764578968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYUME"," userResponse":" KINYUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764580653","data":{"timestamp":" 947764580652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764580963","data":{"timestamp":" 947764580962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764581551","data":{"timestamp":" 947764581551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764582672","data":{"timestamp":" 947764582672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" START_SHIKANE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764584597","data":{"timestamp":" 947764584597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764585982","data":{"timestamp":" 947764585982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" START_YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764587296","data":{"timestamp":" 947764587296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764589898","data":{"timestamp":" 947764589897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764590859","data":{"timestamp":" 947764590859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764592126","data":{"timestamp":" 947764592125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764592251","data":{"timestamp":" 947764592251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764593072","data":{"timestamp":" 947764593071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764593197","data":{"timestamp":" 947764593197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764594271","data":{"timestamp":" 947764594271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764599857","data":{"timestamp":" 947764599857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764600180","data":{"timestamp":" 947764600180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764601559","data":{"timestamp":" 947764601558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_ALIJISIKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764603935","data":{"timestamp":" 947764603935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764604867","data":{"timestamp":" 947764604867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764605956","data":{"timestamp":" 947764605956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" START_YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764606952","data":{"timestamp":" 947764606951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764609533","data":{"timestamp":" 947764609532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764612330","data":{"timestamp":" 947764612330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" HATIMAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764613183","data":{"timestamp":" 947764613183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764614953","data":{"timestamp":" 947764614952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMWACHILIA"," userResponse":" YAKAMWACHILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764615576","data":{"timestamp":" 947764615575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764617839","data":{"timestamp":" 947764617838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764619057","data":{"timestamp":" 947764619057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" START_YAKAMWACHILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764620793","data":{"timestamp":" 947764620792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764621470","data":{"timestamp":" 947764621469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764623161","data":{"timestamp":" 947764623161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMWACHILIA"," userResponse":" START_YAKAMWACHILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764624075","data":{"timestamp":" 947764624075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMWACHILIA"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764626268","data":{"timestamp":" 947764626268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMWACHILIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764627184","data":{"timestamp":" 947764627183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764629204","data":{"timestamp":" 947764629204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764629772","data":{"timestamp":" 947764629771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764630229","data":{"timestamp":" 947764630228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764631249","data":{"timestamp":" 947764631248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764635514","data":{"timestamp":" 947764635514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764636518","data":{"timestamp":" 947764636518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764637134","data":{"timestamp":" 947764637133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764638717","data":{"timestamp":" 947764638717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764641055","data":{"timestamp":" 947764641055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKIA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764641593","data":{"timestamp":" 947764641592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764642373","data":{"timestamp":" 947764642372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764643865","data":{"timestamp":" 947764643864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AKIFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764644914","data":{"timestamp":" 947764644914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOKULA"," userResponse":" ANAPOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764645380","data":{"timestamp":" 947764645379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764646034","data":{"timestamp":" 947764646033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764647156","data":{"timestamp":" 947764647156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAMPA"," userResponse":" ITAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764648302","data":{"timestamp":" 947764648301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSINGI"," userResponse":" MSINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764648494","data":{"timestamp":" 947764648493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764649306","data":{"timestamp":" 947764649306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKALIA"," userResponse":" KUKALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764651804","data":{"timestamp":" 947764651804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIRUKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764658977","data":{"timestamp":" 947764658977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIRUKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764660812","data":{"timestamp":" 947764660811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764662096","data":{"timestamp":" 947764662095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764662108","data":{"timestamp":" 947764662108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764663201","data":{"timestamp":" 947764663201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764666409","data":{"timestamp":" 947764666409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" START_AKIFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764668251","data":{"timestamp":" 947764668251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764671934","data":{"timestamp":" 947764671933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOKULA"," userResponse":" ANAPOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764672914","data":{"timestamp":" 947764672914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764672920","data":{"timestamp":" 947764672920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764673726","data":{"timestamp":" 947764673726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ITAMPA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764675965","data":{"timestamp":" 947764675965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAMPA"," userResponse":" ITAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764676769","data":{"timestamp":" 947764676769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSINGI"," userResponse":" START_MSINGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764677525","data":{"timestamp":" 947764677525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSINGI"," userResponse":" MSINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764679696","data":{"timestamp":" 947764679696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764681535","data":{"timestamp":" 947764681535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKALIA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764684346","data":{"timestamp":" 947764684346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUKALIA"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764685912","data":{"timestamp":" 947764685911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764687916","data":{"timestamp":" 947764687915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764688952","data":{"timestamp":" 947764688951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" ALIPOJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764689594","data":{"timestamp":" 947764689594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHIKA"," userResponse":" KUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764690265","data":{"timestamp":" 947764690264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764691887","data":{"timestamp":" 947764691887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALICHOSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764692902","data":{"timestamp":" 947764692901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764693754","data":{"timestamp":" 947764693754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764694521","data":{"timestamp":" 947764694520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764695404","data":{"timestamp":" 947764695403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764695735","data":{"timestamp":" 947764695735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764698430","data":{"timestamp":" 947764698430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764699441","data":{"timestamp":" 947764699441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764700683","data":{"timestamp":" 947764700683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOJARIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764702910","data":{"timestamp":" 947764702909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764704896","data":{"timestamp":" 947764704896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHIKA"," userResponse":" KUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764704900","data":{"timestamp":" 947764704900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764705696","data":{"timestamp":" 947764705696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOSHIKA"," userResponse":" START_KUSHIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764708754","data":{"timestamp":" 947764708754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOSHIKA"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764710667","data":{"timestamp":" 947764710667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOSHIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764713054","data":{"timestamp":" 947764713054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764715062","data":{"timestamp":" 947764715062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764716025","data":{"timestamp":" 947764716025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764720228","data":{"timestamp":" 947764720228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" START_MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764721800","data":{"timestamp":" 947764721799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764722656","data":{"timestamp":" 947764722656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764725144","data":{"timestamp":" 947764725144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764726324","data":{"timestamp":" 947764726323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHAANZA"," userResponse":" AMESHAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764727253","data":{"timestamp":" 947764727252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGUKA"," userResponse":" KUANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764728356","data":{"timestamp":" 947764728355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764729215","data":{"timestamp":" 947764729215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764731876","data":{"timestamp":" 947764731876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" AMESHAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764732995","data":{"timestamp":" 947764732995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764733599","data":{"timestamp":" 947764733598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHAANZA"," userResponse":" START_AMESHAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764736598","data":{"timestamp":" 947764736598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHAANZA"," userResponse":" AMESHAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764738705","data":{"timestamp":" 947764738705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764743860","data":{"timestamp":" 947764743860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764753968","data":{"timestamp":" 947764753968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764756761","data":{"timestamp":" 947764756760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie nisaidie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764758209","data":{"timestamp":" 947764758209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie nisaidie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764760570","data":{"timestamp":" 947764760569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie nisaidie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" START_AMESHAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764764477","data":{"timestamp":" 947764764477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie nisaidie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764770318","data":{"timestamp":" 947764770318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie nisaidie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764772315","data":{"timestamp":" 947764772314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764773109","data":{"timestamp":" 947764773109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764773645","data":{"timestamp":" 947764773645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764774080","data":{"timestamp":" 947764774079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764774548","data":{"timestamp":" 947764774548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764775729","data":{"timestamp":" 947764775728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" KUMSIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764778260","data":{"timestamp":" 947764778260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764780140","data":{"timestamp":" 947764780140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764782131","data":{"timestamp":" 947764782131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764784349","data":{"timestamp":" 947764784348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764784741","data":{"timestamp":" 947764784741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764787723","data":{"timestamp":" 947764787723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" AMESHAANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764793056","data":{"timestamp":" 947764793056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764795269","data":{"timestamp":" 947764795269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764795537","data":{"timestamp":" 947764795537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764797200","data":{"timestamp":" 947764797200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764797438","data":{"timestamp":" 947764797438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWISHA"," userResponse":" ALIKWISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764797895","data":{"timestamp":" 947764797895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POTEA"," userResponse":" POTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764798141","data":{"timestamp":" 947764798141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" MAWINGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764801911","data":{"timestamp":" 947764801911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764804305","data":{"timestamp":" 947764804305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_ALIKWISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764805875","data":{"timestamp":" 947764805875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764807327","data":{"timestamp":" 947764807326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWISHA"," userResponse":" ALIKWISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764807454","data":{"timestamp":" 947764807453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" POTEA"," userResponse":" ALIKWISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764808568","data":{"timestamp":" 947764808567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POTEA"," userResponse":" POTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764809356","data":{"timestamp":" 947764809355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" START_MAWINGUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764811286","data":{"timestamp":" 947764811286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" MAWINGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764813623","data":{"timestamp":" 947764813622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764814641","data":{"timestamp":" 947764814640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" AKAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764814885","data":{"timestamp":" 947764814884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764815826","data":{"timestamp":" 947764815825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764817106","data":{"timestamp":" 947764817105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764818084","data":{"timestamp":" 947764818083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764818540","data":{"timestamp":" 947764818540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764821616","data":{"timestamp":" 947764821616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764822787","data":{"timestamp":" 947764822787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" AKAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764823615","data":{"timestamp":" 947764823615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764824057","data":{"timestamp":" 947764824057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" START_KISHINDO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764825906","data":{"timestamp":" 947764825905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764826496","data":{"timestamp":" 947764826496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764827798","data":{"timestamp":" 947764827797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764830541","data":{"timestamp":" 947764830540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" START_KIMYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764834811","data":{"timestamp":" 947764834811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764837104","data":{"timestamp":" 947764837104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764839569","data":{"timestamp":" 947764839568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764841843","data":{"timestamp":" 947764841842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" AKAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764842903","data":{"timestamp":" 947764842902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764843392","data":{"timestamp":" 947764843390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764844234","data":{"timestamp":" 947764844233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764845182","data":{"timestamp":" 947764845182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764845801","data":{"timestamp":" 947764845801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764847081","data":{"timestamp":" 947764847081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUNJIKA"," userResponse":" UMEVUNJIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764847823","data":{"timestamp":" 947764847822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOVU"," userResponse":" KOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764848596","data":{"timestamp":" 947764848596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764849618","data":{"timestamp":" 947764849617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764851611","data":{"timestamp":" 947764851610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" KOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764853318","data":{"timestamp":" 947764853318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764855176","data":{"timestamp":" 947764855175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764857037","data":{"timestamp":" 947764857037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" UMEVUNJIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764859156","data":{"timestamp":" 947764859156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764860713","data":{"timestamp":" 947764860712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764862579","data":{"timestamp":" 947764862579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764864084","data":{"timestamp":" 947764864083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764864102","data":{"timestamp":" 947764864101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764866419","data":{"timestamp":" 947764866419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764866487","data":{"timestamp":" 947764866487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764867435","data":{"timestamp":" 947764867435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764868023","data":{"timestamp":" 947764868023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUNJIKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764869786","data":{"timestamp":" 947764869785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUNJIKA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764871849","data":{"timestamp":" 947764871849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUNJIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764872962","data":{"timestamp":" 947764872961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KOVU"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764874521","data":{"timestamp":" 947764874521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KOVU"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764876227","data":{"timestamp":" 947764876226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOVU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764879986","data":{"timestamp":" 947764879986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764882433","data":{"timestamp":" 947764882433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764885570","data":{"timestamp":" 947764885568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAWEZA"," userResponse":" HAJAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764886811","data":{"timestamp":" 947764886810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764887737","data":{"timestamp":" 947764887736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764889615","data":{"timestamp":" 947764889614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAWEZA"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764890429","data":{"timestamp":" 947764890428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAWEZA"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764892188","data":{"timestamp":" 947764892188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAWEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764893159","data":{"timestamp":" 947764893158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764894372","data":{"timestamp":" 947764894372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" HAJAWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764895967","data":{"timestamp":" 947764895966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764897375","data":{"timestamp":" 947764897374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764898925","data":{"timestamp":" 947764898924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764899879","data":{"timestamp":" 947764899879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" URAFIKI"," userResponse":" URAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764900422","data":{"timestamp":" 947764900421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" BAINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764900926","data":{"timestamp":" 947764900926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764901113","data":{"timestamp":" 947764901112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764901762","data":{"timestamp":" 947764901761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764903463","data":{"timestamp":" 947764903463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEPO"," userResponse":" HAKUWEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764903912","data":{"timestamp":" 947764903911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764906343","data":{"timestamp":" 947764906343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764908838","data":{"timestamp":" 947764908837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" URAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764910848","data":{"timestamp":" 947764910848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764912901","data":{"timestamp":" 947764912901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764914653","data":{"timestamp":" 947764914652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764916755","data":{"timestamp":" 947764916755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764919451","data":{"timestamp":" 947764919451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764921871","data":{"timestamp":" 947764921871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764923889","data":{"timestamp":" 947764923888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764924044","data":{"timestamp":" 947764924043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947764990456","data":{"timestamp":" 947764990455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 9057ba92-88b8-478b-aeb4-5be5e5bc498a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765018567","data":{"timestamp":" 947765018567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kw_"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765034894","data":{"timestamp":" 947765034894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nay_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765058908","data":{"timestamp":" 947765058908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_huon_"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765071549","data":{"timestamp":" 947765071549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mume_"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765080785","data":{"timestamp":" 947765080785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fany_"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765091457","data":{"timestamp":" 947765091457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nay_"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765100127","data":{"timestamp":" 947765100127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mliw_"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765108167","data":{"timestamp":" 947765108167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_il_"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765119687","data":{"timestamp":" 947765119687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saut_"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765129121","data":{"timestamp":" 947765129121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zil_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765135718","data":{"timestamp":" 947765135718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zil_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765148959","data":{"timestamp":" 947765148958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" d180ac5d-e8d5-4678-a820-fff3f8a08829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_zil_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765178202","data":{"timestamp":" 947765178202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ko"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765186608","data":{"timestamp":" 947765186608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_gae"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765192471","data":{"timestamp":" 947765192471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_gae"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765203153","data":{"timestamp":" 947765203153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b_eha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765213101","data":{"timestamp":" 947765213101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765224355","data":{"timestamp":" 947765224355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_uo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765239585","data":{"timestamp":" 947765239585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765247875","data":{"timestamp":" 947765247875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_v_gae"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765260429","data":{"timestamp":" 947765260429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d_da"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765268702","data":{"timestamp":" 947765268702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_s_ali"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765284292","data":{"timestamp":" 947765284292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o_yo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765297690","data":{"timestamp":" 947765297690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" b14b17d3-fcc6-4fb8-8848-59ceb037cc79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_o_yo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765312040","data":{"timestamp":" 947765312040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sitawahi_alifuata-sitawahi-mkongojo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sitawahi"," userResponse":" sitawahi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765317324","data":{"timestamp":" 947765317324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tunaweza_sawasawa-tunaweza-kikaango"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tunaweza"," userResponse":" tunaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765322907","data":{"timestamp":" 947765322907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nililala_nililala-lilisema-chochote"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nililala"," userResponse":" lilisema"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765329282","data":{"timestamp":" 947765329282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nililala_nililala-lilisema-chochote"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nililala"," userResponse":" nililala"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765335402","data":{"timestamp":" 947765335402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vibonyeo_mbinguni-vibonyeo-mtonyama"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vibonyeo"," userResponse":" mbinguni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765341318","data":{"timestamp":" 947765341317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vibonyeo_mbinguni-vibonyeo-mtonyama"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vibonyeo"," userResponse":" vibonyeo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765350976","data":{"timestamp":" 947765350975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninanuka_ninanuka-shingoni-nitakufa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninanuka"," userResponse":" ninanuka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765364607","data":{"timestamp":" 947765364607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" halikuwa"," userResponse":" anyamaze"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765371819","data":{"timestamp":" 947765371819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" halikuwa"," userResponse":" halikuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765374093","data":{"timestamp":" 947765374093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 490be691-2f39-4f55-bea7-58ec7d7a65b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765389881","data":{"timestamp":" 947765389881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tunaweza_sawasawa-tunaweza-kikaango"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tunaweza"," userResponse":" tunaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765404189","data":{"timestamp":" 947765404189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" halikuwa"," userResponse":" anyamaze"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765410490","data":{"timestamp":" 947765410490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" halikuwa"," userResponse":" halikuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765420995","data":{"timestamp":" 947765420995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walianza_walianza-sakafuni-alipenda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walianza"," userResponse":" walianza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765426732","data":{"timestamp":" 947765426732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninanuka_ninanuka-shingoni-nitakufa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninanuka"," userResponse":" ninanuka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765432393","data":{"timestamp":" 947765432393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sitawahi_alifuata-sitawahi-mkongojo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sitawahi"," userResponse":" sitawahi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765437535","data":{"timestamp":" 947765437535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_konokono_konokono-shughuli-kimbieni"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" konokono"," userResponse":" konokono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765467094","data":{"timestamp":" 947765467093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nililala_nililala-lilisema-chochote"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nililala"," userResponse":" nililala"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765471637","data":{"timestamp":" 947765471637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hakuwahi_hakuwahi-waliishi-akakataa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hakuwahi"," userResponse":" hakuwahi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765478073","data":{"timestamp":" 947765478073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vibonyeo_mbinguni-vibonyeo-mtonyama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vibonyeo"," userResponse":" vibonyeo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765488442","data":{"timestamp":" 947765488442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ikitokea_ikitokea-kuwapata-hakikuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ikitokea"," userResponse":" ikitokea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765494240","data":{"timestamp":" 947765494238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 659f4cbc-aeee-4dc3-9e9e-30f2ab2e165a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ikitokea_ikitokea-kuwapata-hakikuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765507821","data":{"timestamp":" 947765507820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZATUTEME"," userResponse":" ZATUTEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765519847","data":{"timestamp":" 947765519846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZATUTEME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765521474","data":{"timestamp":" 947765521473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fewebiza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FEWEBIZA"," userResponse":" FEWEBIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765527135","data":{"timestamp":" 947765527134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fewebiza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FEWEBIZA"," userResponse":" FEWEBIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765528743","data":{"timestamp":" 947765528742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fizevana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIZEVANA"," userResponse":" FIZEVANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765532112","data":{"timestamp":" 947765532112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fizevana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIZEVANA"," userResponse":" FIZEVANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765533721","data":{"timestamp":" 947765533721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" salitune"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALITUNE"," userResponse":" SALITUNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765536712","data":{"timestamp":" 947765536711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" salitune"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SALITUNE"," userResponse":" START_SALITUNE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765538635","data":{"timestamp":" 947765538635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" salitune"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALITUNE"," userResponse":" SALITUNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765540249","data":{"timestamp":" 947765540248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" velohuha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VELOHUHA"," userResponse":" VELOHUHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765544045","data":{"timestamp":" 947765544045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" velohuha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VELOHUHA"," userResponse":" VELOHUHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765545622","data":{"timestamp":" 947765545621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" royuwika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROYUWIKA"," userResponse":" ROYUWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765548692","data":{"timestamp":" 947765548692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" royuwika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROYUWIKA"," userResponse":" ROYUWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765550304","data":{"timestamp":" 947765550303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJUJUWA"," userResponse":" NIJUJUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765554235","data":{"timestamp":" 947765554234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJUJUWA"," userResponse":" NIJUJUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765555831","data":{"timestamp":" 947765555830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sosagepa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOSAGEPA"," userResponse":" SOSAGEPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765561673","data":{"timestamp":" 947765561672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sosagepa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOSAGEPA"," userResponse":" SOSAGEPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765563291","data":{"timestamp":" 947765563290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jimidelo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMIDELO"," userResponse":" JIMIDELO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765566438","data":{"timestamp":" 947765566437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jimidelo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMIDELO"," userResponse":" JIMIDELO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765568033","data":{"timestamp":" 947765568032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAZUMUBA"," userResponse":" ZAZUMUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765571630","data":{"timestamp":" 947765571630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAZUMUBA"," userResponse":" START_ZAZUMUBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765574135","data":{"timestamp":" 947765574135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAZUMUBA"," userResponse":" ZAZUMUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765576156","data":{"timestamp":" 947765576155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765576278","data":{"timestamp":" 947765576278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 383deb97-449d-43cc-8941-42553c03b6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAZUMUBA"," userResponse":" ZAZUMUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765595586","data":{"timestamp":" 947765595585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765596322","data":{"timestamp":" 947765596321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765596567","data":{"timestamp":" 947765596566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765597275","data":{"timestamp":" 947765597274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765598266","data":{"timestamp":" 947765598265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765599065","data":{"timestamp":" 947765599064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765599358","data":{"timestamp":" 947765599357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765600386","data":{"timestamp":" 947765600386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765610678","data":{"timestamp":" 947765610678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765611884","data":{"timestamp":" 947765611884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765612998","data":{"timestamp":" 947765612998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765613705","data":{"timestamp":" 947765613704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765614923","data":{"timestamp":" 947765614923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765617131","data":{"timestamp":" 947765617131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765617144","data":{"timestamp":" 947765617144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765618034","data":{"timestamp":" 947765618033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765618431","data":{"timestamp":" 947765618431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765618957","data":{"timestamp":" 947765618956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765621033","data":{"timestamp":" 947765621032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765622034","data":{"timestamp":" 947765622033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765622821","data":{"timestamp":" 947765622820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765623337","data":{"timestamp":" 947765623336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765624266","data":{"timestamp":" 947765624266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765624906","data":{"timestamp":" 947765624905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765625605","data":{"timestamp":" 947765625604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765626434","data":{"timestamp":" 947765626433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" WALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765628805","data":{"timestamp":" 947765628804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" START_WALITAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765629834","data":{"timestamp":" 947765629834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765631801","data":{"timestamp":" 947765631799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765632680","data":{"timestamp":" 947765632680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765634087","data":{"timestamp":" 947765634086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765636125","data":{"timestamp":" 947765636125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765636851","data":{"timestamp":" 947765636850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765638151","data":{"timestamp":" 947765638151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765638311","data":{"timestamp":" 947765638311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765639446","data":{"timestamp":" 947765639445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765640244","data":{"timestamp":" 947765640244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" START_WALIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765641990","data":{"timestamp":" 947765641990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" START_WALIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765643702","data":{"timestamp":" 947765643702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765645460","data":{"timestamp":" 947765645459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765645877","data":{"timestamp":" 947765645876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765646654","data":{"timestamp":" 947765646654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" YUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765647843","data":{"timestamp":" 947765647843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" ANGESTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765648282","data":{"timestamp":" 947765648281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765649335","data":{"timestamp":" 947765649335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765650853","data":{"timestamp":" 947765650853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765651059","data":{"timestamp":" 947765651059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765651969","data":{"timestamp":" 947765651969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" YUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765653267","data":{"timestamp":" 947765653266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" ANGESTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765653860","data":{"timestamp":" 947765653860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765654683","data":{"timestamp":" 947765654683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765657251","data":{"timestamp":" 947765657250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765658094","data":{"timestamp":" 947765658094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765659243","data":{"timestamp":" 947765659242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765661609","data":{"timestamp":" 947765661609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765662184","data":{"timestamp":" 947765662184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765663632","data":{"timestamp":" 947765663631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765665608","data":{"timestamp":" 947765665608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765665946","data":{"timestamp":" 947765665945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765666665","data":{"timestamp":" 947765666665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765667826","data":{"timestamp":" 947765667825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765668052","data":{"timestamp":" 947765668051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765668272","data":{"timestamp":" 947765668271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765669161","data":{"timestamp":" 947765669161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765670756","data":{"timestamp":" 947765670755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765671464","data":{"timestamp":" 947765671463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765671835","data":{"timestamp":" 947765671835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765672829","data":{"timestamp":" 947765672829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765673333","data":{"timestamp":" 947765673332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765673524","data":{"timestamp":" 947765673524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765674339","data":{"timestamp":" 947765674339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765676158","data":{"timestamp":" 947765676157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765677046","data":{"timestamp":" 947765677045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765678748","data":{"timestamp":" 947765678748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765680294","data":{"timestamp":" 947765680294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765681966","data":{"timestamp":" 947765681966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765682927","data":{"timestamp":" 947765682926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765685129","data":{"timestamp":" 947765685129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765686140","data":{"timestamp":" 947765686139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765686920","data":{"timestamp":" 947765686919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765687510","data":{"timestamp":" 947765687509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765688941","data":{"timestamp":" 947765688941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOITANA"," userResponse":" ANAPOITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765689962","data":{"timestamp":" 947765689962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765690354","data":{"timestamp":" 947765690353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765690624","data":{"timestamp":" 947765690624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765690768","data":{"timestamp":" 947765690767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765692179","data":{"timestamp":" 947765692179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765693380","data":{"timestamp":" 947765693379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765694545","data":{"timestamp":" 947765694545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765695492","data":{"timestamp":" 947765695492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765698323","data":{"timestamp":" 947765698323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765699646","data":{"timestamp":" 947765699645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" START_HANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765701286","data":{"timestamp":" 947765701285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765703180","data":{"timestamp":" 947765703179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765704449","data":{"timestamp":" 947765704448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765706772","data":{"timestamp":" 947765706772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOITANA"," userResponse":" ANAPOITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765707602","data":{"timestamp":" 947765707602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" START_SAUTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765708633","data":{"timestamp":" 947765708632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765710580","data":{"timestamp":" 947765710579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765710759","data":{"timestamp":" 947765710759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765711467","data":{"timestamp":" 947765711467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765711665","data":{"timestamp":" 947765711665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765712442","data":{"timestamp":" 947765712442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765713350","data":{"timestamp":" 947765713350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765713972","data":{"timestamp":" 947765713972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" START_SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765715918","data":{"timestamp":" 947765715917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765717271","data":{"timestamp":" 947765717270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765718225","data":{"timestamp":" 947765718225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765719047","data":{"timestamp":" 947765719047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765720880","data":{"timestamp":" 947765720879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765722679","data":{"timestamp":" 947765722679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765724419","data":{"timestamp":" 947765724415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765725247","data":{"timestamp":" 947765725247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765725729","data":{"timestamp":" 947765725729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765726440","data":{"timestamp":" 947765726439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765727192","data":{"timestamp":" 947765727190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765728256","data":{"timestamp":" 947765728255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765729399","data":{"timestamp":" 947765729398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765730262","data":{"timestamp":" 947765730261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765730400","data":{"timestamp":" 947765730400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765731214","data":{"timestamp":" 947765731213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765731812","data":{"timestamp":" 947765731812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765732465","data":{"timestamp":" 947765732465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765734179","data":{"timestamp":" 947765734178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" HUNGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765734834","data":{"timestamp":" 947765734833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765735610","data":{"timestamp":" 947765735610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765736865","data":{"timestamp":" 947765736865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765738167","data":{"timestamp":" 947765738166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765740368","data":{"timestamp":" 947765740367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765745372","data":{"timestamp":" 947765745371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" HUNGURUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765752982","data":{"timestamp":" 947765752982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765752990","data":{"timestamp":" 947765752990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765757924","data":{"timestamp":" 947765757924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765759131","data":{"timestamp":" 947765759131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765759327","data":{"timestamp":" 947765759326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765760053","data":{"timestamp":" 947765760053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765760739","data":{"timestamp":" 947765760739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765761542","data":{"timestamp":" 947765761542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765761848","data":{"timestamp":" 947765761848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765762636","data":{"timestamp":" 947765762636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765762821","data":{"timestamp":" 947765762821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765763731","data":{"timestamp":" 947765763731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765765577","data":{"timestamp":" 947765765577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765766682","data":{"timestamp":" 947765766682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765768410","data":{"timestamp":" 947765768410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765768987","data":{"timestamp":" 947765768987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765770075","data":{"timestamp":" 947765770075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" START_KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765771523","data":{"timestamp":" 947765771523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765773498","data":{"timestamp":" 947765773498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765774275","data":{"timestamp":" 947765774275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765776762","data":{"timestamp":" 947765776762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765778995","data":{"timestamp":" 947765778995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765779885","data":{"timestamp":" 947765779885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765782217","data":{"timestamp":" 947765782217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765782485","data":{"timestamp":" 947765782484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765784171","data":{"timestamp":" 947765784171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765784435","data":{"timestamp":" 947765784435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" HAWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765785305","data":{"timestamp":" 947765785304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765788818","data":{"timestamp":" 947765788818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765790109","data":{"timestamp":" 947765790109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" START_HAWEZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765791249","data":{"timestamp":" 947765791249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765793038","data":{"timestamp":" 947765793038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765793998","data":{"timestamp":" 947765793998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765796378","data":{"timestamp":" 947765796378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765798683","data":{"timestamp":" 947765798683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765798894","data":{"timestamp":" 947765798894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765799444","data":{"timestamp":" 947765799444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765800136","data":{"timestamp":" 947765800136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765800859","data":{"timestamp":" 947765800859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765801682","data":{"timestamp":" 947765801681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765803696","data":{"timestamp":" 947765803696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765804217","data":{"timestamp":" 947765804217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765805405","data":{"timestamp":" 947765805404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765808791","data":{"timestamp":" 947765808791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765813351","data":{"timestamp":" 947765813351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765814781","data":{"timestamp":" 947765814781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765816917","data":{"timestamp":" 947765816916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765817417","data":{"timestamp":" 947765817417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765818093","data":{"timestamp":" 947765818092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765820082","data":{"timestamp":" 947765820082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765823503","data":{"timestamp":" 947765823503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NAFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765824189","data":{"timestamp":" 947765824189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765824603","data":{"timestamp":" 947765824602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765825614","data":{"timestamp":" 947765825613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765826625","data":{"timestamp":" 947765826624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765827513","data":{"timestamp":" 947765827512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765828416","data":{"timestamp":" 947765828415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765829357","data":{"timestamp":" 947765829356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" AKIPUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765829937","data":{"timestamp":" 947765829936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765830488","data":{"timestamp":" 947765830487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765832768","data":{"timestamp":" 947765832768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NAFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765833375","data":{"timestamp":" 947765833374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765834905","data":{"timestamp":" 947765834905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" NAFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765836175","data":{"timestamp":" 947765836175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765837608","data":{"timestamp":" 947765837607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765838595","data":{"timestamp":" 947765838595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765840223","data":{"timestamp":" 947765840222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765841794","data":{"timestamp":" 947765841793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765843484","data":{"timestamp":" 947765843484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765845177","data":{"timestamp":" 947765845176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765846757","data":{"timestamp":" 947765846757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765848988","data":{"timestamp":" 947765848987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765850133","data":{"timestamp":" 947765850133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765851380","data":{"timestamp":" 947765851379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765851671","data":{"timestamp":" 947765851671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765852678","data":{"timestamp":" 947765852677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765854337","data":{"timestamp":" 947765854336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765855400","data":{"timestamp":" 947765855400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765855495","data":{"timestamp":" 947765855495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765857675","data":{"timestamp":" 947765857675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765857991","data":{"timestamp":" 947765857991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765859239","data":{"timestamp":" 947765859238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765860840","data":{"timestamp":" 947765860839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765862391","data":{"timestamp":" 947765862391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765862980","data":{"timestamp":" 947765862979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765862999","data":{"timestamp":" 947765862998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765863503","data":{"timestamp":" 947765863502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765866098","data":{"timestamp":" 947765866098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" UNARINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765866819","data":{"timestamp":" 947765866818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765867898","data":{"timestamp":" 947765867898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765868567","data":{"timestamp":" 947765868566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHOVA"," userResponse":" KHOVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765869758","data":{"timestamp":" 947765869757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765870753","data":{"timestamp":" 947765870751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765872626","data":{"timestamp":" 947765872625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765873815","data":{"timestamp":" 947765873815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765875526","data":{"timestamp":" 947765875525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765875825","data":{"timestamp":" 947765875825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765876934","data":{"timestamp":" 947765876934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765877754","data":{"timestamp":" 947765877753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765878861","data":{"timestamp":" 947765878860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765879969","data":{"timestamp":" 947765879969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHOVA"," userResponse":" KHOVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765879982","data":{"timestamp":" 947765879981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765880079","data":{"timestamp":" 947765880079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765882229","data":{"timestamp":" 947765882228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" ISITOSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765883221","data":{"timestamp":" 947765883220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765883759","data":{"timestamp":" 947765883758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765884107","data":{"timestamp":" 947765884107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765885327","data":{"timestamp":" 947765885326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAFRIKA"," userResponse":" MWAFRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765887106","data":{"timestamp":" 947765887106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" START_ISITOSHE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765889424","data":{"timestamp":" 947765889424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" START_ISITOSHE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765891115","data":{"timestamp":" 947765891115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765892729","data":{"timestamp":" 947765892729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765893871","data":{"timestamp":" 947765893871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" ISITOSHE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765894599","data":{"timestamp":" 947765894598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765895005","data":{"timestamp":" 947765895005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765896115","data":{"timestamp":" 947765896115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWAFRIKA"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765897073","data":{"timestamp":" 947765897073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWAFRIKA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765898689","data":{"timestamp":" 947765898688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAFRIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765900889","data":{"timestamp":" 947765900888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765901691","data":{"timestamp":" 947765901690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765902699","data":{"timestamp":" 947765902698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765903471","data":{"timestamp":" 947765903470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765904150","data":{"timestamp":" 947765904149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDA"," userResponse":" KUSHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765904363","data":{"timestamp":" 947765904362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765904994","data":{"timestamp":" 947765904993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765905566","data":{"timestamp":" 947765905565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765907050","data":{"timestamp":" 947765907050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765907448","data":{"timestamp":" 947765907448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765908351","data":{"timestamp":" 947765908351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765909042","data":{"timestamp":" 947765909042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765909545","data":{"timestamp":" 947765909545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDA"," userResponse":" START_KUSHINDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765911483","data":{"timestamp":" 947765911483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDA"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765913030","data":{"timestamp":" 947765913029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765914331","data":{"timestamp":" 947765914331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765916187","data":{"timestamp":" 947765916187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765917084","data":{"timestamp":" 947765917084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765918391","data":{"timestamp":" 947765918390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765921416","data":{"timestamp":" 947765921414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASTAHILI"," userResponse":" NINASTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765921942","data":{"timestamp":" 947765921942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765922670","data":{"timestamp":" 947765922669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765924656","data":{"timestamp":" 947765924656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINASTAHILI"," userResponse":" START_NINASTAHILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765925638","data":{"timestamp":" 947765925638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NINASTAHILI"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765927445","data":{"timestamp":" 947765927444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASTAHILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765929110","data":{"timestamp":" 947765929109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" MWAFRIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765930792","data":{"timestamp":" 947765930792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765931261","data":{"timestamp":" 947765931261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765933045","data":{"timestamp":" 947765933044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765933923","data":{"timestamp":" 947765933922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765934410","data":{"timestamp":" 947765934410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765935102","data":{"timestamp":" 947765935102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765936142","data":{"timestamp":" 947765936141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765936861","data":{"timestamp":" 947765936860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765938919","data":{"timestamp":" 947765938918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765939633","data":{"timestamp":" 947765939633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765939994","data":{"timestamp":" 947765939994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765940402","data":{"timestamp":" 947765940401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765942121","data":{"timestamp":" 947765942121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765943565","data":{"timestamp":" 947765943564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765946068","data":{"timestamp":" 947765946068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765947196","data":{"timestamp":" 947765947196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765947839","data":{"timestamp":" 947765947839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765949828","data":{"timestamp":" 947765949828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765952106","data":{"timestamp":" 947765952105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765952715","data":{"timestamp":" 947765952714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUENDA"," userResponse":" HUENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765953615","data":{"timestamp":" 947765953615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765954445","data":{"timestamp":" 947765954444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765955864","data":{"timestamp":" 947765955863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765958094","data":{"timestamp":" 947765958094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765958988","data":{"timestamp":" 947765958987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUENDA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765961159","data":{"timestamp":" 947765961159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUENDA"," userResponse":" START_NAFIKIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765962649","data":{"timestamp":" 947765962648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765964334","data":{"timestamp":" 947765964334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765969203","data":{"timestamp":" 947765969203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765972058","data":{"timestamp":" 947765972058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765972161","data":{"timestamp":" 947765972161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" START_LINAPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765973705","data":{"timestamp":" 947765973705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" START_LINAPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765975811","data":{"timestamp":" 947765975810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765977173","data":{"timestamp":" 947765977173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765977999","data":{"timestamp":" 947765977999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765978150","data":{"timestamp":" 947765978149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUKINI"," userResponse":" BUKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765978718","data":{"timestamp":" 947765978718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765978806","data":{"timestamp":" 947765978806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" BUKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765979070","data":{"timestamp":" 947765979070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765979362","data":{"timestamp":" 947765979362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765979428","data":{"timestamp":" 947765979427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765979725","data":{"timestamp":" 947765979724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765979924","data":{"timestamp":" 947765979923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765980145","data":{"timestamp":" 947765980145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765980178","data":{"timestamp":" 947765980178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765980616","data":{"timestamp":" 947765980615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765980718","data":{"timestamp":" 947765980717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765980834","data":{"timestamp":" 947765980833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765980958","data":{"timestamp":" 947765980958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIANI"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765996812","data":{"timestamp":" 947765996811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947765996930","data":{"timestamp":" 947765996930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" 84f627a9-02ce-4cc6-a9db-0477625dbe13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIANI"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766011955","data":{"timestamp":" 947766011954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766012693","data":{"timestamp":" 947766012692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766012941","data":{"timestamp":" 947766012940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766013650","data":{"timestamp":" 947766013649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766014642","data":{"timestamp":" 947766014641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766015443","data":{"timestamp":" 947766015442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766015739","data":{"timestamp":" 947766015738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766016766","data":{"timestamp":" 947766016766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766030021","data":{"timestamp":" 947766030021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766033475","data":{"timestamp":" 947766033475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766039726","data":{"timestamp":" 947766039726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766044735","data":{"timestamp":" 947766044734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766047447","data":{"timestamp":" 947766047446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766054626","data":{"timestamp":" 947766054625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766055902","data":{"timestamp":" 947766055902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766057787","data":{"timestamp":" 947766057787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766058864","data":{"timestamp":" 947766058864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766060950","data":{"timestamp":" 947766060950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766063033","data":{"timestamp":" 947766063032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766064032","data":{"timestamp":" 947766064031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766064821","data":{"timestamp":" 947766064821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766065339","data":{"timestamp":" 947766065338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766066270","data":{"timestamp":" 947766066269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766066912","data":{"timestamp":" 947766066911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766067613","data":{"timestamp":" 947766067612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766068443","data":{"timestamp":" 947766068442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" WALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766071738","data":{"timestamp":" 947766071738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766073365","data":{"timestamp":" 947766073365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766075327","data":{"timestamp":" 947766075326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766075496","data":{"timestamp":" 947766075496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766077129","data":{"timestamp":" 947766077129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766078797","data":{"timestamp":" 947766078796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766079353","data":{"timestamp":" 947766079352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766080068","data":{"timestamp":" 947766080068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766081971","data":{"timestamp":" 947766081970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" WALIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766086922","data":{"timestamp":" 947766086922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766087733","data":{"timestamp":" 947766087733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766089042","data":{"timestamp":" 947766089042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766089643","data":{"timestamp":" 947766089643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766090552","data":{"timestamp":" 947766090552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766091313","data":{"timestamp":" 947766091312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" START_WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766093089","data":{"timestamp":" 947766093088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766098790","data":{"timestamp":" 947766098790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" WALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766100526","data":{"timestamp":" 947766100526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766100940","data":{"timestamp":" 947766100940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766101720","data":{"timestamp":" 947766101719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" YUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766102909","data":{"timestamp":" 947766102908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" ANGESTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766103345","data":{"timestamp":" 947766103344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766104404","data":{"timestamp":" 947766104404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766106135","data":{"timestamp":" 947766106135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766107527","data":{"timestamp":" 947766107526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766110093","data":{"timestamp":" 947766110093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766111413","data":{"timestamp":" 947766111413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766112187","data":{"timestamp":" 947766112187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766113744","data":{"timestamp":" 947766113744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766115440","data":{"timestamp":" 947766115439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766116117","data":{"timestamp":" 947766116117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" ANGESTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766116120","data":{"timestamp":" 947766116120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766117112","data":{"timestamp":" 947766117112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766119697","data":{"timestamp":" 947766119696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766120531","data":{"timestamp":" 947766120531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766121665","data":{"timestamp":" 947766121665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766124971","data":{"timestamp":" 947766124971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766129397","data":{"timestamp":" 947766129397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766137049","data":{"timestamp":" 947766137049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766140999","data":{"timestamp":" 947766140999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766142144","data":{"timestamp":" 947766142144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766142950","data":{"timestamp":" 947766142950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766143275","data":{"timestamp":" 947766143275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766143612","data":{"timestamp":" 947766143611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766144103","data":{"timestamp":" 947766144102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766144327","data":{"timestamp":" 947766144326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766144556","data":{"timestamp":" 947766144556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766144773","data":{"timestamp":" 947766144773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766146451","data":{"timestamp":" 947766146449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766146617","data":{"timestamp":" 947766146616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766176604","data":{"timestamp":" 947766176603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" bea69d21-c7ef-40b5-8baa-008e0bf54224"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766192552","data":{"timestamp":" 947766192552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lefarako_tujubiri-lefarako-pukamebu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lefarako"," userResponse":" lefarako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766197777","data":{"timestamp":" 947766197777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_heyiyiku_heyiyiku-yogetoje-wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" heyiyiku"," userResponse":" heyiyiku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766203165","data":{"timestamp":" 947766203164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jigogiki_jigogiki-yeduyamo-dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jigogiki"," userResponse":" jigogiki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766226247","data":{"timestamp":" 947766226246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_lazububu-mehayehe-fewebiza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" lazububu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766232061","data":{"timestamp":" 947766232061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tetafeki_tetafeki-jigogiki-fopozife"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tetafeki"," userResponse":" tetafeki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766238759","data":{"timestamp":" 947766238759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_yeduyamo-towamuvu-wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wovudaku"," userResponse":" wovudaku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766246899","data":{"timestamp":" 947766246899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_zatuteme_fizevana-nijujuwa-zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zatuteme"," userResponse":" zatuteme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766256540","data":{"timestamp":" 947766256540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_timumugu_lozeyimu-timumugu-honojuye"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" timumugu"," userResponse":" timumugu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766268704","data":{"timestamp":" 947766268704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_towamuvu_honojuye-lefarako-towamuvu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" towamuvu"," userResponse":" towamuvu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766285778","data":{"timestamp":" 947766285778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_velohuha_velohuha-fopozife-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" velohuha"," userResponse":" velohuha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766291553","data":{"timestamp":" 947766291552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e246b2af-9b6f-4233-a9ad-495636885827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_velohuha_velohuha-fopozife-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766325938","data":{"timestamp":" 947766325938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fizevana_fizevana-honojuye-tetafeki"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fizevana"," userResponse":" fizevana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766332978","data":{"timestamp":" 947766332978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" zazumuba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766357514","data":{"timestamp":" 947766357514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" hasavefi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766368661","data":{"timestamp":" 947766368660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" lazububu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766381973","data":{"timestamp":" 947766381972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wovudaku"," userResponse":" jimidelo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766389873","data":{"timestamp":" 947766389873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wovudaku"," userResponse":" wovudaku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766405913","data":{"timestamp":" 947766405913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavunahe_kavunahe-timumugu-pukamebu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavunahe"," userResponse":" timumugu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766413121","data":{"timestamp":" 947766413121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavunahe_kavunahe-timumugu-pukamebu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavunahe"," userResponse":" kavunahe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766424319","data":{"timestamp":" 947766424319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pabihako_lazububu-pabihako-kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pabihako"," userResponse":" pabihako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766430353","data":{"timestamp":" 947766430353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jimidelo_zatuteme-burigema-jimidelo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jimidelo"," userResponse":" jimidelo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766437961","data":{"timestamp":" 947766437961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosihife_heyiyiku-salitune-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosihife"," userResponse":" heyiyiku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766444438","data":{"timestamp":" 947766444438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosihife_heyiyiku-salitune-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosihife"," userResponse":" kosihife"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766453129","data":{"timestamp":" 947766453129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dovimahu_heyiyiku-velohuha-dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dovimahu"," userResponse":" heyiyiku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766460467","data":{"timestamp":" 947766460466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dovimahu_heyiyiku-velohuha-dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dovimahu"," userResponse":" dovimahu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766468587","data":{"timestamp":" 947766468586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasavefi_burigema-hasavefi-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasavefi"," userResponse":" burigema"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766475012","data":{"timestamp":" 947766475011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasavefi_burigema-hasavefi-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasavefi"," userResponse":" hasavefi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766480755","data":{"timestamp":" 947766480755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_zazumuba_honojuye-lefarako-zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zazumuba"," userResponse":" zazumuba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766486539","data":{"timestamp":" 947766486538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" a39b2744-477c-4d3e-9b25-6b04388d5153"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_zazumuba_honojuye-lefarako-zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766501842","data":{"timestamp":" 947766501842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fizevana_fizevana-honojuye-tetafeki"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fizevana"," userResponse":" fizevana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766509325","data":{"timestamp":" 947766509325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasavefi_burigema-hasavefi-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasavefi"," userResponse":" hasavefi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766520544","data":{"timestamp":" 947766520544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jimidelo_zatuteme-burigema-jimidelo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jimidelo"," userResponse":" jimidelo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766545251","data":{"timestamp":" 947766545251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavunahe_kavunahe-timumugu-pukamebu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavunahe"," userResponse":" pukamebu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766565252","data":{"timestamp":" 947766565252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavunahe_kavunahe-timumugu-pukamebu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavunahe"," userResponse":" timumugu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766574169","data":{"timestamp":" 947766574169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavunahe_kavunahe-timumugu-pukamebu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavunahe"," userResponse":" kavunahe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766579795","data":{"timestamp":" 947766579795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_zazumuba_honojuye-lefarako-zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zazumuba"," userResponse":" zazumuba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766585096","data":{"timestamp":" 947766585096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dovimahu_heyiyiku-velohuha-dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dovimahu"," userResponse":" heyiyiku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766591437","data":{"timestamp":" 947766591437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dovimahu_heyiyiku-velohuha-dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dovimahu"," userResponse":" dovimahu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766612582","data":{"timestamp":" 947766612582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wovudaku"," userResponse":" heyiyiku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766619564","data":{"timestamp":" 947766619563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wovudaku"," userResponse":" wovudaku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766699257","data":{"timestamp":" 947766699256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" zazumuba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766708473","data":{"timestamp":" 947766708472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" hasavefi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766715020","data":{"timestamp":" 947766715020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" lazububu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766722999","data":{"timestamp":" 947766722999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pabihako_lazububu-pabihako-kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pabihako"," userResponse":" pabihako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766730562","data":{"timestamp":" 947766730561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosihife_heyiyiku-salitune-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosihife"," userResponse":" kosihife"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766736342","data":{"timestamp":" 947766736340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kosihife_heyiyiku-salitune-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766754778","data":{"timestamp":" 947766754777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_141534"," gameId":" e9428665-6c39-4ecd-b3e5-b1a3713cb652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kosihife_heyiyiku-salitune-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}